''/O `/O Nick/PERSON Fallon/PERSON ''/O '/O is/O a/O fictional/O character/O on/O the/O American/O soap/O opera/O ''/O Days/O of/O Our/O Lives/O ''/O ./O
The/O role/O was/O played/O by/O Blake/PERSON Berris/PERSON from/O November/O 7/O ,/O 2006/O ,/O to/O January/O 15/O ,/O 2009/O ./O
In/O May/O 2012/O ,/O it/O was/O announced/O that/O Berris/PERSON would/O return/O to/O the/O series/O ./O
He/O returned/O on/O August/O 27/O ,/O 2012/O ./O
His/O final/O air/O date/O was/O May/O 12/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O when/O the/O character/O was/O killed/O in/O a/O whodunit/O murder/O mystery/O ./O
Nick/PERSON ,/O the/O son/O of/O Joshua/PERSON Fallon/PERSON and/O Jessica/PERSON Blake/PERSON -LRB-/O the/O daughter/O of/O Marie/PERSON Horton/PERSON and/O the/O granddaughter/O of/O Alice/PERSON Horton/PERSON -RRB-/O ,/O came/O to/O Salem/LOCATION to/O get/O to/O know/O his/O Horton/PERSON relatives/O ./O
His/O medical/O knowledge/O and/O intelligence/O were/O put/O to/O the/O test/O when/O he/O was/O asked/O to/O help/O save/O Kayla/PERSON Brady/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O suffering/O from/O a/O rare/O ailment/O ./O
He/O succeeded/O in/O saving/O Kayla/PERSON ,/O and/O found/O himself/O intrigued/O by/O Chelsea/PERSON Brady/PERSON ./O
Nick/PERSON created/O an/O online/O identity/O to/O chat/O with/O Chelsea/PERSON in/O an/O attempt/O to/O get/O her/O to/O fall/O for/O him/O ,/O and/O provided/O a/O picture/O of/O a/O handsome/O colleague/O of/O his/O when/O she/O pushes/O to/O know/O what/O he/O looks/O like/O ./O
Later/O ,/O Nick/PERSON helped/O Chelsea/PERSON get/O money/O to/O Shawn/PERSON and/O Belle/PERSON who/O were/O on/O the/O run/O with/O their/O daughter/O Claire/PERSON in/O Toronto/LOCATION ,/O Canada/LOCATION ./O
Nick/PERSON 's/O clever/O and/O brave/O actions/O on/O this/O mission/O caused/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION to/O take/O interest/O in/O Nick/PERSON as/O more/O than/O a/O friend/O ./O
However/O ,/O shortly/O after/O returning/O from/O Canada/LOCATION ,/O Chelsea/PERSON discovered/O that/O Nick/PERSON was/O her/O online/O love/O ./O
She/O was/O devastated/O and/O saw/O Nick/PERSON 's/O actions/O as/O a/O malicious/O trick/O ,/O thinking/O that/O Nick/PERSON used/O the/O online/O lover/O to/O secretly/O mock/O her/O while/O she/O revealed/O her/O inner/O thoughts/O and/O feelings/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O
She/O tearfully/O told/O Nick/PERSON that/O she/O never/O wanted/O to/O see/O him/O again/O ./O
Hurt/O ,/O Nick/PERSON had/O an/O affair/O with/O Chelsea/PERSON 's/O mother/O Billie/PERSON Reed/PERSON ,/O who/O ,/O under/O the/O influence/O of/O alcohol/O seduced/O him/O ./O
Billie/PERSON and/O he/O both/O regretted/O it/O ,/O and/O swore/O never/O to/O tell/O anyone/O ./O
When/O Nick/PERSON saved/O Chelsea/PERSON from/O getting/O raped/O by/O Dr./O Reibert/PERSON ,/O whom/O she/O had/O been/O dating/O to/O spite/O Nick/PERSON ,/O she/O forgave/O him/O ./O
Nick/PERSON began/O tutoring/O her/O in/O math/O and/O this/O led/O to/O them/O dating/O ./O
Unfortunately/O ,/O Chelsea/PERSON soon/O discovered/O Nick/PERSON and/O Billie/PERSON 's/O one-night/O stand/O and/O their/O relationship/O was/O again/O in/O turmoil/O ./O
Then/O ,/O when/O Willow/PERSON Stark/PERSON accidentally/O set/O Bo/PERSON and/O Hope/O 's/O house/O on/O fire/O ,/O she/O panicked/O and/O attempted/O to/O frame/O Chelsea/PERSON by/O planting/O her/O hairbrush/O at/O the/O crime/O scene/O ./O
At/O Chelsea/LOCATION 's/O cry/O of/O innocence/O ,/O Nick/PERSON risked/O his/O medical/O career/O by/O stealing/O the/O hairbrush/O out/O of/O the/O forensics/O lab/O ./O
Chelsea/PERSON was/O so/O grateful/O ,/O she/O was/O able/O to/O forgive/O Nick/PERSON for/O his/O indiscretion/O with/O Billie/PERSON ,/O and/O they/O soon/O rekindled/O their/O romance/O ./O
Later/O ,/O Willow/PERSON emerged/O as/O a/O threat/O to/O Nick/PERSON and/O Chelsea/PERSON 's/O happiness/O ./O
When/O Nick/PERSON stole/O the/O hairbrush/O ,/O it/O left/O Willow/PERSON as/O the/O only/O suspect/O for/O the/O fire/O ./O
Nick/PERSON felt/O sorry/O for/O Willow/PERSON and/O lent/O her/O money/O ./O
Willow/PERSON asked/O for/O more/O money/O ,/O and/O Nick/PERSON leased/O an/O apartment/O for/O her/O and/O gave/O her/O his/O credit/O card/O to/O use/O for/O her/O and/O her/O baby/O ./O
Willow/PERSON used/O Nick/PERSON 's/O credit/O card/O excessively/O ,/O then/O she/O called/O Nick/PERSON and/O blackmailed/O him/O into/O giving/O her/O more/O money/O ,/O credit/O cards/O ,/O and/O all/O kinds/O of/O stuff/O ./O
Nick/PERSON later/O went/O to/O the/O beach/O to/O meet/O Willow/PERSON and/O they/O got/O in/O an/O argument/O and/O a/O struggle/O that/O lead/O to/O Willow/O falling/O ,/O and/O hitting/O her/O head/O on/O a/O log/O ./O
Nick/PERSON tried/O to/O revive/O her/O but/O Willow/PERSON died/O ./O
He/O found/O the/O hairbrush/O in/O Willow/LOCATION 's/O possession/O and/O buried/O it/O in/O the/O sand/O on/O the/O beach/O before/O calling/O for/O help/O ./O
While/O Nick/PERSON was/O investigated/O by/O detective/O Roman/PERSON Brady/PERSON ,/O he/O convinced/O Chelsea/PERSON to/O go/O to/O the/O beach/O and/O destroy/O the/O hairbrush/O ./O
Roman/O eventually/O learned/O the/O truth/O ,/O and/O gave/O both/O Chelsea/PERSON and/O Nick/PERSON a/O pass/O by/O closing/O the/O investigation/O ./O
Nick/PERSON was/O also/O blackmailed/O by/O Kate/PERSON Roberts/PERSON into/O making/O Sami/PERSON 's/O amniocentesis/O say/O that/O EJ/O was/O the/O father/O of/O Sami/PERSON 's/O twins/O ./O
Nick/PERSON saved/O Sami/PERSON Brady/PERSON and/O Lucas/PERSON Roberts/PERSON from/O a/O bomb/O that/O Dr./O Rolf/PERSON planted/O ,/O sustaining/O head/O injuries/O in/O the/O process/O ./O
While/O suffering/O from/O a/O concussion/O ,/O Nick/PERSON went/O to/O Las/LOCATION Vegas/LOCATION and/O married/O a/O woman/O named/O Cassandra/PERSON Arvin/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O using/O the/O alias/O ``/O China/O Lee/O ''/O ./O
Arvin/PERSON was/O eventually/O persuaded/O to/O sign/O annulment/O papers/O ./O
Then/O she/O was/O arrested/O and/O went/O to/O jail/O for/O soliciting/O ,/O leaving/O Nick/PERSON with/O custody/O of/O her/O two/O sons/O ,/O Artemis/ORGANIZATION and/O Demarquette/O ./O
Nick/PERSON deduced/O that/O Artemis/ORGANIZATION and/O Demarquette/PERSON were/O not/O really/O China/PERSON Lee/PERSON 's/O children/O ,/O which/O she/O confirmed/O upon/O her/O release/O from/O jail/O ./O
She/O had/O been/O hired/O to/O protect/O the/O boys/O ,/O but/O refused/O to/O retake/O custody/O of/O them/O ./O
A/O man/O named/O Umar/PERSON Maboud/PERSON came/O to/O Nick/PERSON 's/O home/O and/O claimed/O that/O he/O worked/O for/O the/O boys/O '/O parents/O and/O had/O been/O sent/O to/O bring/O them/O home/O ./O
Nick/PERSON did/O not/O trust/O Maboud/PERSON ,/O and/O Jeremy/PERSON Horton/PERSON -LRB-/O who/O was/O staying/O with/O Nick/PERSON at/O the/O time/O -RRB-/O successfully/O fought/O him/O off/O ./O
Weeks/O later/O ,/O Chelsea/PERSON was/O abducted/O and/O was/O permitted/O to/O use/O her/O cell/O phone/O only/O to/O contact/O Nick/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O directed/O to/O come/O to/O a/O designated/O location/O ,/O alone/O ./O
When/O he/O did/O ,/O the/O kidnapper/O offered/O a/O hostage/O exchange/O :/O Artemis/ORGANIZATION and/O Demarquette/O for/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION ./O
Unbeknownst/O to/O the/O man/O ,/O the/O boys/O had/O followed/O Nick/PERSON to/O the/O warehouse/O ,/O but/O were/O able/O to/O escape/O ./O
While/O Nick/PERSON worked/O to/O avert/O the/O detonation/O of/O what/O turned/O out/O to/O be/O a/O fake/O bomb/O ,/O Artemis/ORGANIZATION and/O Demarquette/PERSON were/O rescued/O by/O Umar/PERSON Maboud/PERSON ./O
Maboud/O really/O was/O in/O the/O employ/O of/O the/O boys/O '/O parents/O ,/O who/O were/O wealthy/O foreigners/O with/O many/O enemies/O ./O
Having/O secured/O political/O asylum/O ,/O they/O wanted/O to/O be/O reunited/O with/O their/O sons/O ;/O Chelsea/PERSON 's/O abduction/O had/O been/O a/O ploy/O by/O the/O family/O 's/O enemies/O ./O
Nick/PERSON agreed/O to/O let/O Artemis/ORGANIZATION and/O Demarquette/O go/O ./O
Nick/PERSON and/O Chelsea/PERSON got/O back/O together/O ./O
He/O helped/O Chelsea/PERSON find/O proof/O that/O Ford/PERSON Decker/PERSON was/O the/O campus/O rapist/O by/O breaking/O into/O Ford/ORGANIZATION 's/O room/O in/O order/O to/O take/O photographs/O of/O his/O drugs/O and/O journal/O ./O
After/O the/O campus/O rapist/O situation/O was/O resolved/O ,/O Chelsea/PERSON and/O Nick/PERSON grew/O apart/O because/O of/O her/O attraction/O to/O Dr./O Daniel/PERSON Jonas/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O two/O eventually/O broke/O up/O ./O
Nick/PERSON then/O began/O working/O on/O a/O research/O project/O involving/O alternative/O fuel/O sources/O and/O began/O a/O relationship/O with/O Max/PERSON Brady/PERSON 's/O half/O sister/O ,/O Melanie/PERSON Layton/PERSON ./O
Nick/PERSON ultimately/O began/O stalking/O her/O and/O was/O then/O revealed/O to/O be/O the/O killer/O of/O Trent/PERSON Robbins/PERSON ,/O Max/PERSON and/O Melanie/PERSON 's/O father/O ./O
On/O January/O 14/O ,/O 2009/O ,/O Nick/PERSON was/O tried/O for/O the/O murder/O of/O Trent/PERSON Robbins/PERSON ./O
Maggie/PERSON and/O Melanie/PERSON gave/O testimony/O as/O to/O why/O Nick/PERSON should/O not/O be/O put/O in/O jail/O for/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O life/O ./O
The/O judge/O agreed/O and/O gave/O Nick/PERSON the/O sentence/O of/O 2/O to/O 5/O years/O in/O a/O facility/O and/O 18/O months/O for/O good/O behavior/O ./O
Nick/PERSON was/O thankful/O to/O Melanie/PERSON for/O her/O testimony/O as/O Melanie/PERSON told/O Nick/PERSON that/O she/O forgave/O him/O because/O deep/O down/O he/O was/O a/O good/O person/O ./O
On/O January/O 15/O ,/O 2009/O ,/O Chelsea/PERSON comes/O from/O the/O hospital/O to/O the/O courthouse/O ./O
Nick/PERSON tells/O Chelsea/PERSON he/O 's/O sorry/O for/O everything/O and/O tells/O her/O to/O move/O on/O with/O her/O life/O ./O
Chelsea/PERSON tearfully/O tells/O Nick/PERSON that/O he/O will/O always/O have/O a/O piece/O of/O her/O heart/O and/O that/O he/O can/O focus/O on/O getting/O better/O ./O
On/O August/O 27/O ,/O 2012/O ,/O Nick/PERSON returned/O to/O Salem/LOCATION and/O ,/O still/O in/O jail/O ,/O had/O a/O parole/O hearing/O ./O
Having/O been/O recently/O kidnapped/O ,/O Melanie/PERSON did/O not/O know/O how/O she/O felt/O ./O
Against/O the/O advice/O of/O her/O family/O ,/O Melanie/PERSON decided/O that/O Nick/PERSON really/O had/O changed/O ,/O but/O wanted/O him/O to/O stay/O away/O from/O her/O ./O
Nick/PERSON was/O released/O and/O threatened/O by/O Chad/LOCATION to/O stay/O away/O ./O
Caroline/PERSON forgave/O Nick/PERSON and/O gave/O him/O a/O job/O at/O the/O Brady/LOCATION Pub/LOCATION ./O
Chad/PERSON beat/O Nick/PERSON up/O after/O believing/O that/O he/O had/O Melanie/PERSON ,/O since/O he/O had/O her/O scarf/O ./O
Later/O ,/O Nick/PERSON met/O Melanie/PERSON 's/O former/O friend/O Gabi/PERSON ,/O and/O they/O started/O dating/O ./O 
On/O November/O 14/O ,/O Gabi/PERSON found/O out/O she/O was/O pregnant/O with/O her/O gay/O ex-boyfriend/O Will/PERSON Horton/PERSON 's/O baby/O ./O
Nick/PERSON agreed/O with/O Gabi/PERSON and/O Will/O that/O he/O would/O raise/O the/O child/O ,/O and/O that/O he/O and/O Gabi/PERSON would/O get/O married/O ./O
Nick/PERSON and/O Gabi/PERSON had/O a/O church/O wedding/O ,/O but/O before/O they/O could/O be/O pronounced/O husband/O and/O wife/O ,/O Chad/PERSON objected/O ,/O saying/O that/O Nick/PERSON was/O not/O the/O father/O of/O Gabi/PERSON 's/O baby/O ,/O and/O it/O finally/O came/O out/O that/O Will/O was/O the/O father/O ./O
At/O a/O later/O date/O ,/O Nick/PERSON blackmailed/PERSON Will/PERSON to/O give/O up/O his/O parental/O rights/O to/O Gabi/PERSON 's/O baby/O ,/O by/O threatening/O to/O tell/O that/O Will/PERSON was/O the/O one/O who/O shot/O EJ/O ./O
With/O several/O other/O people/O around/O ,/O including/O Sami/PERSON ,/O Lucas/PERSON ,/O EJ/O ,/O Sonny/PERSON ,/O and/O an/O attorney/O Nick/PERSON brought/O ,/O Will/PERSON signed/O the/O agreement/O ./O
Nick/PERSON and/O Gabi/PERSON married/O in/O a/O private/O ceremony/O ./O
Only/O later/O did/O Gabi/PERSON learn/O that/O Will/PERSON gave/O up/O rights/O to/O the/O baby/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O not/O learn/O about/O the/O blackmail/O ,/O though/O Will/PERSON tells/O her/O he/O did/O not/O want/O to/O do/O it/O ./O
Nick/PERSON had/O memories/O of/O something/O terrible/O that/O happened/O in/O jail/O ,/O possibly/O involving/O another/O inmate/O ,/O Vargas/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O recently/O released/O and/O getting/O help/O from/O the/O church/O to/O adjust/O to/O regular/O life/O ./O
The/O terrible/O thing/O is/O later/O revealed/O to/O be/O repeated/O prison/O rape/O by/O another/O inmate/O named/O Jensen/PERSON ./O
Nick/PERSON was/O kidnapped/O ,/O along/O with/O Gabi/PERSON ,/O and/O held/O hostage/O by/O Jensen/PERSON ./O
Will/O and/O Sonny/PERSON saved/O them/O ,/O with/O Will/O getting/O shot/O in/O the/O process/O ./O
Nick/PERSON then/O tried/O to/O make/O things/O right/O ,/O considering/O that/O Will/O almost/O died/O to/O save/O him/O ,/O and/O agreed/O to/O have/O Will/PERSON 's/O name/O on/O Arianna/PERSON 's/O birth/O certificate/O ./O
Nick/PERSON told/O Gabi/PERSON the/O truth/O about/O his/O rape/O and/O about/O blackmailing/O Will/O ./O
Nick/PERSON was/O fired/O by/O Kate/PERSON in/O June/O 2013/O ./O
In/O August/O 2013/O ,/O when/O his/O parole/O was/O up/O ,/O he/O was/O told/O to/O vacate/O the/O Kiriakis/O mansion/O immediately/O by/O Victor/PERSON Kiriakis/PERSON ./O
Nick/PERSON became/O obsessed/O with/O Gabi/PERSON and/O got/O her/O a/O modeling/O job/O in/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ,/O where/O he/O would/O be/O as/O well/O ,/O hoping/O that/O they/O could/O be/O together/O ./O
After/O Gabi/PERSON yelled/O at/O him/O for/O interfering/O in/O her/O life/O ,/O he/O followed/O her/O to/O the/O park/O where/O he/O tried/O to/O rape/O her/O ./O
Gabi/PERSON hit/O him/O in/O the/O head/O with/O a/O rock/O and/O Sami/PERSON and/O Kate/PERSON helped/O her/O drag/O Nick/PERSON 's/O body/O to/O the/O river/O where/O he/O briefly/O awoke/O before/O apparently/O drowning/O on/O November/O 27/O ./O
On/O January/O 24/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O Nick/PERSON arrived/O at/O Gabi/PERSON and/O Will/O 's/O daughter/O 's/O baptism/O revealing/O that/O he/O had/O not/O drowned/O ./O
He/O appeared/O reformed/O but/O soon/O blackmailed/O Kate/PERSON into/O hiring/O him/O ./O
Nick/PERSON also/O manipulated/O Gabi/PERSON into/O giving/O him/O another/O chance/O ,/O and/O she/O felt/O that/O she/O must/O do/O so/O or/O risk/O going/O to/O jail/O for/O trying/O to/O murder/O Nick/PERSON ./O
Nick/PERSON later/O manipulated/O EJ/O and/O Sami/PERSON into/O giving/O Gabi/PERSON a/O modeling/O contract/O with/O Countess/PERSON Wilhelmina/PERSON ./O
Later/O ,/O Nick/PERSON got/O involved/O in/O a/O custody/O agreement/O of/O Will/O and/O Gabi/PERSON 's/O daughter/O Ari/PERSON ,/O pushing/O Gabi/PERSON to/O only/O let/O Will/PERSON see/O his/O daughter/O at/O times/O she/O allowed/O it/O ./O
Will/O and/O Sonny/PERSON felt/O that/O Nick/PERSON would/O manipulate/O Gabi/PERSON until/O he/O had/O Gabi/PERSON and/O Ari/PERSON to/O himself/O ./O
In/O the/O meantime/O ,/O EJ/PERSON DiMera/PERSON found/O out/O that/O someone/O had/O pictures/O of/O him/O and/O Abigail/PERSON Deveraux/PERSON kissing/O sent/O to/O his/O house/O ./O
EJ/O and/O Abigail/PERSON later/O found/O out/O that/O Nick/PERSON was/O behind/O it/O ./O
On/O May/O 9/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O Nick/PERSON was/O shot/O three/O times/O ,/O once/O in/O the/O back/O and/O twice/O in/O the/O chest/O ,/O and/O he/O died/O on/O May/O 12/O with/O an/O open/O investigation/O into/O who/O was/O responsible/O ./O
On/O May/O 30/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O It/O was/O revealed/O that/O it/O was/O Gabi/PERSON Hernandez/PERSON who/O shot/O Nick/PERSON ./O
*/O from/O soapcentral.com/O ''/O `/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O '/O -LRB-/O -RRB-/O is/O a/O fictional/O character/O created/O by/O French/O writers/O Marcel/PERSON Allain/PERSON -LRB-/O 1885-1969/O -RRB-/O and/O Pierre/PERSON Souvestre/PERSON -LRB-/O 1874-1914/O -RRB-/O ./O
One/O of/O the/O most/O popular/O characters/O in/O the/O history/O of/O French/O crime/O fiction/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON was/O created/O in/O 1911/O and/O appeared/O in/O a/O total/O of/O 32/O volumes/O written/O by/O the/O two/O collaborators/O ,/O then/O a/O subsequent/O 11/O volumes/O written/O by/O Allain/PERSON alone/O after/O Souvestre/PERSON 's/O death/O ./O
The/O character/O was/O also/O the/O basis/O of/O various/O film/O ,/O television/O ,/O and/O comic/O book/O adaptations/O ./O
In/O the/O history/O of/O crime/O fiction/O ,/O he/O represents/O a/O transition/O from/O Gothic/O novel/O villains/O of/O the/O 19th/O century/O to/O modern-day/O serial/O killers/O ./O
The/O books/O and/O movies/O that/O came/O out/O in/O quick/O succession/O anticipate/O current/O production/O methods/O of/O Hollywood/LOCATION ,/O in/O two/O respects/O :/O First/O ,/O the/O authors/O distributed/O the/O writing/O among/O themselves/O ;/O their/O ``/O working/O method/O was/O to/O draw/O up/O the/O general/O plot/O between/O them/O and/O then/O go/O off/O and/O write/O alternate/O chapters/O independently/O of/O each/O other/O ,/O meeting/O up/O to/O tie/O the/O two-halves/O of/O the/O story/O together/O in/O the/O final/O chapter/O ./O ''/O
This/O approach/O allowed/O the/O authors/O to/O produce/O almost/O one/O novel/O per/O month/O ./O
Second/O ,/O the/O movie/O rights/O to/O the/O books/O were/O immediately/O snapped/O up/O ./O
Such/O a/O system/O ensured/O that/O the/O film/O studio/O could/O produce/O sequels/O reliably/O ./O
New/O Fantomas/O stories/O set/O in/O period/O are/O currently/O appearing/O in/O Bold/ORGANIZATION Venture/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION '/O pulp/O magazine/O AWESOMED/O Tales/O ./O
The/O popular/O depiction/O of/O Fant¶mas/O as/O wearing/O a/O blue/O mask/O ,/O black/O gloves/O ,/O and/O using/O technological/O devices/O did/O not/O originate/O in/O the/O novels/O ,/O but/O is/O a/O result/O of/O the/O popularity/O of/O the/O trilogy/O of/O Fant¶mas/O movies/O directed/O by/O AndrÚ/PERSON Hunebelle/PERSON in/O the/O 1960s/O ./O
The/O trilogy/O ,/O which/O started/O in/O 1963/O with/O Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1964/O film/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O departed/O considerably/O from/O the/O novels/O by/O giving/O the/O story/O a/O more/O comedic/O tone/O ,/O and/O by/O making/O Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O played/O by/O Jean/PERSON Marais/PERSON -RRB-/O more/O of/O a/O James/PERSON Bond/PERSON enemy/O ./O
Despite/O these/O discrepancies/O ,/O the/O blue-masked/O Fant¶mas/O is/O arguably/O the/O one/O that/O is/O most/O easily/O remembered/O ./O
./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON wears/O his/O iconic/O black/O hood/O and/O black/O leotard/O ,/O more/O sinister/O features/O than/O the/O traditional/O gentleman/O thief/O 's/O domino/O mask/O and/O tuxedo/O ./O
Fant¶mas/O is/O a/O criminal/O genius/O ,/O ruthless/O and/O particularly/O elusive/O ./O
As/O described/O by/O Sch³tt/PERSON -LRB-/O 2003/O -RRB-/O in/O her/O analysis/O of/O French/O crime/O fiction/O literature/O ,/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION is/O the/O cause/O of/O almost/O any/O unsolved/O crime/O ,/O a/O merciless/O criminal/O who/O can/O get/O away/O with/O his/O evil/O deeds/O by/O impersonating/O pretty/O much/O anyone/O ./O
He/O is/O obsessively/O chased/O by/O Inspector/O Juve/PERSON ,/O who/O is/O generally/O the/O only/O one/O able/O to/O see/O Fant¶mas/PERSON 's/O tracks/O ./O
Fant¶mas/O was/O introduced/O a/O few/O years/O after/O ArsÞne/PERSON Lupin/PERSON ,/O another/O well-known/O thief/O ./O
But/O whereas/O Lupin/PERSON draws/O the/O line/O at/O murder/O ,/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION has/O no/O such/O qualms/O and/O is/O shown/O as/O a/O sociopath/O who/O enjoys/O killing/O in/O a/O sadistic/O fashion/O ./O
He/O is/O totally/O ruthless/O ,/O gives/O no/O mercy/O ,/O and/O is/O loyal/O to/O none/O ,/O not/O even/O his/O own/O children/O ./O
He/O is/O a/O master/O of/O disguise/O ,/O always/O appearing/O under/O an/O assumed/O identity/O ,/O often/O that/O of/O a/O person/O whom/O he/O has/O murdered/O ./O
Fant¶mas/O makes/O use/O of/O bizarre/O and/O improbable/O techniques/O in/O his/O crimes/O ,/O such/O as/O plague-infested/O rats/O ,/O giant/O snakes/O ,/O and/O rooms/O that/O fill/O with/O sand/O ./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON 's/O background/O remains/O vague/O ./O
He/O might/O be/O of/O British/O and/or/O French/O ancestry/O ./O
He/O appears/O to/O have/O been/O born/O in/O 1867/O ./O
In/O the/O books/O ,/O it/O is/O established/O that/O c./O 1892/O ,/O the/O man/O who/O later/O became/O Fant¶mas/PERSON called/O himself/O Archduke/O Juan/PERSON North/PERSON and/O operated/O in/O the/O German/O Principality/O of/O Hesse-Weimar/O ./O
There/O he/O fathered/O a/O child/O ,/O Vladimir/PERSON ,/O with/O an/O unidentified/O noblewoman/O ./O
In/O circumstances/O unrevealed/O ,/O he/O was/O arrested/O and/O sent/O to/O prison/O ./O
C./O 1895/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON was/O in/O India/LOCATION ./O
There/O ,/O an/O unidentified/O European/O woman/O gave/O birth/O to/O a/O baby/O girl/O ,/O HÚlÞne/PERSON ,/O whose/O father/O might/O be/O Fant¶mas/O or/O an/O Indian/O Prince/O who/O was/O Fant¶mas/O '/O acolyte/O ./O
The/O girl/O was/O raised/O in/O South/LOCATION Africa/LOCATION ./O
In/O 1897/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON was/O in/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION of/LOCATION America/LOCATION and/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O
There/O ,/O he/O ruined/O his/O then-business/O partner/O ,/O Etienne/PERSON Rambert/PERSON ./O
In/O 1899/O ,/O he/O fought/O in/O the/O Second/O Boer/O War/O in/O South/LOCATION Africa/LOCATION under/O the/O name/O of/O Gurn/LOCATION ./O
He/O fought/O in/O the/O Transvaal/LOCATION as/O an/O artillery/O sergeant/O under/O the/O command/O of/O Lord/O Roberts/PERSON ./O
He/O became/O aide-de-camp/O to/O Lord/O Edward/PERSON Beltham/PERSON of/O Scottwell/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION and/O fell/O in/O love/O with/O his/O younger/O wife/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Maud/PERSON Beltham/PERSON ./O
Upon/O their/O return/O to/O Europe/LOCATION ,/O soon/O before/O the/O first/O novel/O begins/O -LRB-/O c./O 1900/O -RRB-/O ,/O Gurn/PERSON and/O Lady/PERSON Beltham/PERSON were/O surprised/O in/O their/O Paris/LOCATION love/O nest/O ,/O Rue/PERSON Levert/PERSON ,/O by/O her/O husband/O ./O
Lord/O Beltham/PERSON was/O about/O to/O shoot/O Maud/PERSON when/O Gurn/PERSON hit/O him/O with/O a/O hammer/O then/O strangled/O him/O ./O
Fant¶mas/O then/O impersonated/O Etienne/PERSON Rambert/PERSON and/O framed/O his/O son/O ,/O Charles/PERSON ,/O for/O a/O murder/O he/O had/O committed/O ./O
As/O Etienne/PERSON ,/O he/O persuaded/O Charles/PERSON to/O go/O into/O hiding/O ,/O but/O the/O young/O man/O was/O soon/O found/O out/O by/O French/O police/O detective/O Juve/PERSON ,/O truly/O obsessed/O with/O the/O capture/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
Juve/PERSON knew/O that/O Charles/PERSON was/O innocent/O and/O gave/O him/O a/O new/O identity/O :/O journalist/O Jer¶me/PERSON Fandor/PERSON who/O is/O employed/O at/O the/O newspaper/O ''/O La/O Capitale/O ''/O ./O
Juve/ORGANIZATION later/O arrested/O Gurn/PERSON and/O ,/O at/O his/O trial/O ,/O brought/O forward/O a/O convincing/O argument/O that/O Gurn/PERSON and/O Fant¶mas/O were/O one/O and/O the/O same/O ,/O though/O the/O evidence/O was/O too/O circumstantial/O to/O make/O a/O real/O case/O ./O
On/O the/O eve/O of/O his/O execution/O ,/O Gurn/Fant/O ¶mas/O escaped/O from/O custody/O by/O being/O replaced/O by/O an/O actor/O who/O had/O modelled/O the/O appearance/O of/O his/O latest/O character/O after/O him/O and/O was/O guillotined/O in/O his/O place/O ./O
Lady/O Beltham/PERSON remained/O constantly/O torn/O between/O her/O passion/O for/O the/O villain/O and/O her/O horror/O at/O his/O criminal/O schemes/O ./O
She/O eventually/O committed/O suicide/O in/O 1910/O ./O
Fandor/O fell/O in/O love/O with/O HÚlÞne/PERSON and/O ,/O despite/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION 's/O repeated/O attempts/O to/O break/O them/O up/O ,/O married/O her/O ./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON 's/O evil/O son/O ,/O Vladimir/PERSON ,/O reappeared/O in/O 1911/O ./O
Vladimir/PERSON 's/O girlfriend/O was/O murdered/O by/O Fant¶mas/PERSON and/O Vladimir/PERSON himself/O was/O eventually/O shot/O by/O Juve/PERSON ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O '/O :/O A/O criminal/O genius/O ,/O known/O by/O many/O nicknames/O ,/O such/O as/O ``/O the/O ``/O master/O of/O everything/O and/O everyone/O ,/O ''/O the/O ``/O torturer/O ''/O or/O the/O ``/O elusive/O ''/O ,/O and/O whose/O face/O and/O true/O identity/O remain/O unknown/O ./O
A/O ruthless/O criminal/O ,/O he/O wo/O n't/O hesitate/O to/O torture/O and/O kill/O to/O achieve/O his/O goals/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Juve/O ''/O '/O :/O An/O inspector/O in/O the/O S¹retÚ/O of/O Paris/LOCATION ,/O he/O is/O the/O sworn/O archenemy/O of/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION ,/O whom/O he/O pursues/O obsessively/O ./O
The/O intelligent/O and/O stubborn/O Juve/ORGANIZATION is/O completely/O devoted/O to/O capture/O or/O kill/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O JÚr¶me/O Fandor/O ''/O '/O :/O a/O former/O victim/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O he/O was/O originally/O named/O Charles/PERSON Rambert/PERSON ./O
Fant¶mas/O killed/O his/O parents/O and/O then/O framed/O him/O as/O the/O killer/O ./O
Juve/ORGANIZATION is/O the/O only/O one/O to/O understand/O his/O wrong/O accusation/O and/O then/O provides/O him/O with/O the/O identity/O of/O journalist/O Fandor/PERSON so/O as/O to/O prevent/O him/O from/O going/O to/O jail/O and/O to/O use/O his/O help/O in/O capturing/O the/O murderer/O ./O
He/O falls/O in/O love/O with/O HÚlÞne/PERSON ./O
*/O ''/O `/O HÚlÞne/O ''/O '/O :/O She/O is/O the/O beautiful/O stepdaughter/O of/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION ,/O who/O might/O even/O be/O her/O biological/O father/O ./O
The/O criminal/O protects/O her/O jealously/O ./O
She/O falls/O in/O love/O with/O with/O J./PERSON Fandor/PERSON ,/O and/O is/O engaged/O to/O marry/O him/O ,/O eventually/O helping/O her/O fiancÚ/O to/O fight/O the/O criminal/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Lady/O Maud/PERSON Beltham/PERSON ''/O '/O :/O The/O wife/O of/O Lord/O Beltham/PERSON ,/O she/O becomes/O the/O lover/O of/O Fant¶mas/PERSON ,/O towards/O whom/O she/O feels/O both/O passionate/O love/O and/O repulsion/O for/O his/O many/O crimes/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Bouzille/O ''/O '/O :/O a/O streetwise/O tramp/O who/O is/O often/O helping/O Juve/ORGANIZATION and/O Fandor/LOCATION ,/O and/O even/O Fant¶mas/O on/O occasion/O ,/O and/O provides/O comic/O relief/O in/O the/O series/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O The/O Beadle/O ''/O '/O :/O a/O thug/O and/O companion/O of/O Fant¶mas/O who/O earns/O his/O nickname/O after/O his/O custom/O of/O taking/O the/O money/O of/O passers-by/O by/O smashing/O their/O heads/O against/O the/O pavement/O ,/O he/O is/O the/O more/O notorious/O of/O Fant¶mas/O gang/O of/O Apaches/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Mother/O Toulouche/O ''/O '/O :/O An/O old/O woman/O who/O is/O a/O sort/O of/O leader/O among/O Fant¶mas/PERSON '/O Apaches/O ./O
She/O is/O portrayed/O as/O an/O equally/O ruthless/O killer/O and/O thug/O ./O
*/O 1/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1915/O ;/O retransl/O ./O
1986/O -RRB-/O */O 2/O ./O ''/O
Juve/O contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1916/O as/O ''/O ''/O ;/O retransl/O ./O
1987/O as/O ''/O The/O Silent/O Executioner/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 3/O ./O ''/O
Le/PERSON Mort/PERSON qui/O Tue/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1917/O as/O ''/O ''/O ;/O retransl/O ./O
2008/O as/O ''/O The/O Corpse/O who/O Kills/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 4/O ./O ''/O
L'Agent/O Secret/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1917/O as/O ''/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 5/O ./O ''/O
Un/O Roi/O Prisonnier/O de/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1918/O as/O ''/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 6/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Policier/O Apache/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1924/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O The/O Long/O Arm/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 7/O ./O ''/O
Le/LOCATION Pendu/LOCATION de/LOCATION Londres/LOCATION ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1920/O as/O ''/O Slippery/O as/O Sin/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 8/O ./O ''/O
La/O Fille/O de/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
2006/O by/O Mark/PERSON P./PERSON Steele/PERSON as/O ''/O The/O Daughter/O of/O Fantomas/O ''/O -RRB-/O -LRB-/O ISBN/O 1932983562/O -RRB-/O */O 9/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Fiacre/O de/O Nuit/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O -RRB-/O */O 10/O ./O ''/O
La/O Main/O CoupÚe/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1911/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1924/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O The/O Limb/O of/O Satan/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 11/O ./O ''/O
L'Arrestation/O de/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 12/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Magistrat/O Cambrioleur/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 13/O ./O ''/O
La/O LivrÚe/O du/O Crime/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 14/O ./O ''/O
La/PERSON Mort/PERSON de/PERSON Juve/PERSON ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 15/O ./O ''/O
L'EvadÚe/O de/O Saint-Lazare/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 16/O ./O ''/O
La/O Disparition/O de/O Fandor/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 17/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Mariage/O de/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 18/O ./O ''/O
L'Assassin/O de/O Lady/O Beltham/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 19/O ./O ''/O
La/O GuÛpe/O Rouge/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 20/O ./O ''/O
Les/PERSON Souliers/PERSON du/O Mort/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 21/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Train/O Perdu/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 22/O ./O ''/O
Les/ORGANIZATION Amours/ORGANIZATION d'un/O Prince/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 23/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Bouquet/O Tragique/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1912/O -RRB-/O */O 24/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Jockey/O MasquÚ/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 25/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Cercueil/O Vide/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 26/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Faiseur/O de/O Reines/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 27/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Cadavre/O GÚant/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 28/O ./O ''/O
Le/PERSON Voleur/PERSON d'Or/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 29/O ./O ''/O
La/O SÚrie/O Rouge/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 30/O ./O ''/O
L'H¶tel/O du/O Crime/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 31/O ./O ''/O
La/O Cravate/O de/O Chanvre/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 32/O ./O ''/O
La/O Fin/O de/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 33/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O est-il/O ressuscitÚ/O ?/O ''/O
-LRB-/O 1925/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1925/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O The/O Lord/O of/O Terror/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 34/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O ,/O Roi/O des/O RecÚleurs/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1926/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1926/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O Juve/ORGANIZATION in/O the/O Dock/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 35/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O en/O Danger/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1926/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1926/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O Captured/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 36/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O prend/O sa/O Revanche/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1926/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1927/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O The/O Revenge/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 37/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O Attaque/O Fandor/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1926/O ;/O transl/O ./O
1928/O by/O Alfred/PERSON Allinson/PERSON as/O ''/O Bulldog/O and/O Rats/O ''/O -RRB-/O */O 38/O ./O ''/O
Si/O c/O '/O Útait/O Fant¶mas/O ?/O ''/O
-LRB-/O 1933/O -RRB-/O */O 39/O ./O ''/O
Oui/O ,/O c'est/O Fant¶mas/O !/O ''/O
-LRB-/O 1934/O -RRB-/O */O 40/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O Joue/O et/O Gagne/PERSON ''/O -LRB-/O 1935/O -RRB-/O */O 41/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O Rencontre/O l'Amour/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1946/O -RRB-/O */O 42/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O Vole/O des/O Blondes/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1948/O -RRB-/O */O 43/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O MÞne/O le/O Bal/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1963/O -RRB-/O */O The/O original/O covers/O by/O Gino/PERSON Starace/PERSON are/O often/O considered/O works/O of/O lurid/O genius/O in/O themselves/O and/O may/O be/O seen/O at/O the/O ``/O Fant¶mas/O Lives/O ''/O site/O ./O
The/O first/O Fant¶mas/O book/O cover/O ,/O showing/O a/O contemplative/O masked/O man/O dressed/O in/O evening/O dress/O and/O holding/O a/O dagger/O ,/O boldly/O stepping/O over/O Paris/LOCATION ,/O is/O so/O well/O known/O that/O it/O has/O become/O a/O visual/O clichÚ/O ./O
*/O The/O novel/O ''/O The/O Yellow/O Document/O ,/O or/O Fant¶mas/O of/O Berlin/LOCATION ''/O by/O Marcel/PERSON Allain/PERSON -LRB-/O 1919/O -RRB-/O ,/O despite/O its/O title/O ,/O is/O not/O a/O Fant¶mas/O novel/O ./O
*/O The/O last/O novel/O written/O by/O Allain/PERSON was/O published/O as/O a/O newspaper/O serial/O ,/O but/O never/O appeared/O in/O book/O form/O ./O
*/O During/O the/O 1980s/O ,/O the/O first/O two/O novels/O of/O the/O series/O were/O published/O in/O revised/O English/O translations/O :/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O appeared/O in/O 1986/O with/O an/O introduction/O by/O American/O poet/O John/PERSON Ashbery/PERSON ;/O and/O ''/O Juve/O contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O appeared/O in/O 1987/O under/O the/O title/O ''/O The/O Silent/O Executioner/O ''/O ,/O with/O an/O introduction/O by/O American/O artist/O Edward/PERSON Gorey/PERSON ./O
./O
In/O the/O original/O illustration/O for/O the/O first/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O book/O cover/O ,/O the/O character/O holds/O a/O bloody/O dagger/O in/O his/O free/O hand.It/O was/O also/O used/O for/O the/O DVD/O box/O cover/O ,/O but/O this/O time/O Fant¶mas/O stamps/O over/O a/O photo/O of/O modern-day/O Paris/LOCATION ./O
*/O 1/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1913/O serial/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 2/O ./O ''/O
Juve/O Contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 3/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Mort/O Qui/O Tue/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1913/O -RRB-/O */O 4/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O Contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1914/O -RRB-/O */O 5/O ./O ''/O
Le/O Faux/O Magistrat/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1914/O -RRB-/O The/O silent/O film/O pioneer/O Louis/PERSON Feuillade/PERSON directed/O five/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O serials/O starring/O RenÚ/PERSON Navarre/PERSON as/O Fant¶mas/PERSON ,/O BrÚon/PERSON as/O Juve/ORGANIZATION ,/O Georges/PERSON Melchior/PERSON as/O Fandor/O ,/O and/O RenÚe/PERSON Carl/PERSON as/O Lady/PERSON Beltham/PERSON ./O
They/O are/O regarded/O as/O masterpieces/O of/O silent/O film/O ./O
His/O later/O serial/O ''/O Les/O Vampires/O ''/O ,/O which/O concerns/O the/O eponymous/O crime/O syndicate/O -LRB-/O and/O not/O actual/O vampires/O -RRB-/O is/O also/O reminiscent/O of/O the/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O series/O ./O
There/O was/O a/O 1920/O 20-episode/O American/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1920/O serial/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O serial/O directed/O by/O Edward/PERSON Sedgwick/PERSON starring/O Edward/PERSON Roseman/PERSON as/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O which/O bore/O little/O resemblance/O to/O the/O French/O series/O ./O
In/O it/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON 's/O nemesis/O is/O detective/O Fred/PERSON Dixon/PERSON ,/O played/O by/O John/PERSON Willard/PERSON ./O
It/O was/O partially/O released/O in/O France/LOCATION -LRB-/O 12/O episodes/O only/O -RRB-/O under/O the/O title/O ''/O Les/O Exploits/O de/O Diabolos/O ''/O -LRB-/O ''/O The/O Exploits/O of/O Diabolos/O ''/O -RRB-/O ./O
A/O novelization/O of/O this/O serial/O was/O written/O by/O David/PERSON Lee/PERSON White/ORGANIZATION for/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION Coat/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION under/O the/O title/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O in/O America/LOCATION ''/O in/O 2007/O ./O
*/O 6/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1932/O film/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1932/O -RRB-/O ,/O directed/O by/O Paul/PERSON Fejos/PERSON |/O Paul/PERSON FÚjos/PERSON with/O Jean/PERSON Galland/PERSON as/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
*/O 7/O ./O ''/O
Monsieur/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1937/O -RRB-/O ,/O directed/O by/O Ernst/PERSON Moerman/PERSON ./O
*/O 8/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1946/O film/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1946/O -RRB-/O ,/O directed/O by/O Jean/PERSON Sacha/PERSON with/O Marcel/PERSON Herrand/PERSON as/O Fantomas/O ./O
*/O 9/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1948/O -RRB-/O ,/O directed/O by/O Robert/PERSON Vernay/PERSON with/O Maurice/PERSON Teynac/PERSON as/O Fantomas/O ./O
*/O 10/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1964/O film/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1964/O -RRB-/O ,/O the/O first/O of/O three/O films/O directed/O by/O AndrÚ/PERSON Hunebelle/PERSON ;/O with/O Jean/PERSON Marais/PERSON as/O both/O Fant¶mas/O and/O Fandor/PERSON ,/O Louis/PERSON de/PERSON FunÞs/PERSON as/O Juve/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O MylÞne/PERSON Demongeot/PERSON as/O Fandor/PERSON 's/O bride/O ,/O the/O photographer/O HÚlÞne/PERSON ./O
Their/O tone/O was/O generally/O much/O more/O light-hearted/O than/O the/O novels/O '/O and/O the/O characters/O were/O updated/O in/O a/O James/O Bond-like/O style/O including/O Bond-type/O gadgets/O like/O the/O flying/O CitroÙn/O DS/O of/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION with/O retractable/O wings/O that/O converts/O to/O an/O airplane/O ./O
*/O 11/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O se/O dÚcha¯ne/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1965/O -RRB-/O */O 12/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O contre/O Scotland/O Yard/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1966/O -RRB-/O */O 13/O ./O ''/O
Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O in/O development/O -RRB-/O ,/O directed/O by/O Christophe/PERSON Gans/PERSON ./O
A/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O series/O of/O four/O 90-minute/O episodes/O was/O produced/O in/O 1980/O starring/O Helmut/PERSON Berger/PERSON as/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O Jacques/PERSON Dufilho/PERSON as/O Juve/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O Gayle/PERSON Hunnicutt/PERSON as/O Lady/PERSON Beltham/PERSON ./O
Episodes/O 1/O and/O 4/O were/O directed/O by/O Claude/PERSON Chabrol/PERSON ;/O episodes/O 2/O and/O 3/O by/O Luis/PERSON Bu±uel/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O Juan/PERSON Luis/PERSON Bu±uel/PERSON ./O
The/O Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1964/O film/O -RRB-/O |/O French/O movie/O version/O of/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O appears/O in/O the/O Czechoslovakian/O 1979-1981/O children/O fantasy/O series/O ''/O Arabela/O ''/O as/O well/O as/O its/O sequel/O series/O ''/O Arabela/O se/O vraci/O ''/O ,/O performed/O respectively/O by/O actors/O FrantiÜek/PERSON Peterka/PERSON and/O Pavel/PERSON Nov²/PERSON ./O
In/O this/O version/O ,/O he/O does/O not/O perform/O a/O villain/O 's/O role/O ,/O but/O becomes/O an/O ally/O and/O friend/O of/O the/O protagonists/O ./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON also/O has/O a/O cameo/O appearance/O in/O the/O Czech/O children/O 's/O series/O ''/O Lucie/PERSON ,/O postrach/O ulice/O ''/O as/O a/O TV/O character/O ,/O where/O he/O resembles/O his/O original/O 1911/O book/O serial/O covers/O '/O depiction/O ./O
*/O ``/O Fant¶mas/O contre/O les/O Nains/O ''/O ./O
A/O weekly/O color/O page/O written/O by/O Marcel/PERSON Allain/PERSON and/O drawn/O by/O Santini/PERSON was/O published/O in/O ''/O Gavroche/O ''/O #/O 24-30/O -LRB-/O 1941/O -RRB-/O ./O
This/O series/O was/O interrupted/O because/O of/O censorship/O ;/O a/O sequel/O ,/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O et/O l'Enfer/O Sous-Marin/O ''/O was/O written/O but/O not/O published/O ./O
*/O A/O daily/O ``/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O strip/O drawn/O by/O Pierre/PERSON Tabary/PERSON was/O syndicated/O by/O Opera/ORGANIZATION Mundi/ORGANIZATION from/O November/O 1957/O to/O March/O 1958/O -LRB-/O 192/O strips/O in/O total/O -RRB-/O ,/O adapting/O the/O first/O two/O novels/O ./O
*/O Seventeen/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O fumetti/O magazines/O adapting/O books/O 1/O ,/O 2/O ,/O 3/O ,/O and/O 5/O were/O published/O by/O Del/LOCATION Duca/LOCATION in/O 1962/O and/O 1963/O ./O
*/O A/O new/O weekly/O ``/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O color/O page/O ,/O written/O by/O AgnÞs/PERSON Guilloteau/PERSON and/O drawn/O by/O Jacques/PERSON Taillefer/PERSON ,/O was/O again/O syndicated/O by/O Opera/ORGANIZATION Mundi/ORGANIZATION in/O 1969/O and/O published/O in/O ''/O Jours/O de/O France/O ''/O ./O
*/O Finally/O ,/O a/O series/O of/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O graphic/O novels/O written/O by/O L./PERSON Dellisse/PERSON and/O drawn/O by/O Claude/PERSON Laverdure/PERSON were/O published/O by/O Belgian/O publisher/O Claude/PERSON Lefrancq/PERSON :/O ''/O L'Affaire/PERSON Beltham/PERSON ''/O -LRB-/O 1990/O -RRB-/O ,/O ''/O Juve/ORGANIZATION contre/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1991/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O ''/O Le/PERSON Mort/PERSON qui/O Tue/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1995/O -RRB-/O ./O
During/O the/O 1960s/O the/O Mexican/O comics/O publisher/O Editorial/PERSON Novaro/PERSON produced/O a/O ''/O Fantomas/O ,/O La/ORGANIZATION Amenaza/ORGANIZATION Elegante/ORGANIZATION ''/O -LRB-/O Fantomas/O ,/O the/O Elegant/O Threat/O -RRB-/O comic/O book/O series/O that/O became/O popular/O throughout/O Latin/LOCATION America/LOCATION ./O
This/O was/O apparently/O meant/O to/O be/O the/O same/O character/O ,/O although/O rewritten/O as/O a/O hero/O ,/O and/O with/O no/O acknowledgement/O to/O the/O original/O French/O books/O or/O films/O ./O
Perhaps/O as/O a/O way/O to/O make/O the/O original/O French/O character/O more/O attuned/O to/O Latin/O American/O audiences/O who/O crave/O justice/O avengers/O in/O fiction/O and/O national/O politics/O ./O
It/O is/O not/O known/O if/O this/O was/O done/O with/O or/O without/O legal/O permission/O ./O
This/O Fant¶mas/PERSON was/O a/O thief/O who/O committed/O spectacular/O robberies/O just/O for/O the/O thrill/O of/O it/O ,/O and/O wore/O a/O white/O skintight/O mask/O all/O the/O time/O or/O a/O variety/O of/O disguises/O so/O his/O true/O face/O was/O never/O shown/O to/O his/O nemeses/O ./O
The/O character/O was/O also/O pursued/O by/O the/O authorities/O ,/O in/O his/O case/O mainly/O by/O a/O French/O police/O inspector/O named/O Gerard/PERSON ./O
His/O mask/O in/O the/O Latin/O American/O version/O -/O which/O was/O clearly/O inspired/O by/O the/O black/O mask/O worn/O by/O the/O Italian/O comic/O book/O criminal/O ''/O Diabolik/O ''/O -/O and/O his/O use/O of/O it/O ,/O seems/O to/O have/O been/O influenced/O by/O the/O popular/O images/O generated/O by/O Mexican/O wrestling/O ./O
The/O Latin/O American/O Fant¶mas/O mixed/O Italian/O and/O Mexican/O styles/O creating/O a/O wikt/O :/O hybrid/O |/O hybrid/O -/O just/O as/O the/O flag/O of/O Mexico/LOCATION and/O the/O flag/O of/O Italy/LOCATION are/O made/O different/O by/O the/O central/O emblem/O of/O the/O Aztec/O pictogram/O for/O Tenochtitlan/LOCATION on/O the/O Mexican/O flag/O ./O
The/O French/O character/O wore/O a/O black/O mask/O like/O his/O Italian/O inspiration/O ,/O the/O Latin/O American/O a/O white/O mask/O like/O Mexican/O wrestling/O hero/O Santo/PERSON -LRB-/O literally/O `/O saint/O '/O in/O Spanish/O -RRB-/O -/O Italy/LOCATION faces/O Africa/LOCATION home/O to/O a/O majority/O Black/O population/O ,/O Mexico/LOCATION the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION mostly/O with/O a/O majority/O White/O population/O ./O
These/O characters/O had/O to/O remain/O relevant/O and/O mysterious/O to/O their/O specific/O geographical/O regions/O to/O survive/O and/O succeed/O ./O
Apparently/O the/O series/O was/O also/O influenced/O by/O the/O ''/O James/PERSON Bond/PERSON ''/O movies/O ,/O as/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O equipped/O with/O advanced/O technology/O created/O by/O a/O scientist/O called/O Professor/O Semo/PERSON ,/O had/O all/O kind/O of/O adventures/O around/O the/O world/O ,/O and/O even/O fought/O other/O ,/O more/O cruel/O criminals/O ./O
The/O Latin/O American/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O created/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O encompassed/O the/O aesthetic/O of/O both/O the/O British/O James/PERSON Bond/PERSON and/O American/O Hugh/PERSON Hefner/PERSON ,/O who/O created/O ''/O Playboy/O ''/O magazine/O ,/O with/O a/O necessary/O dose/O of/O traditional/O Latin/O American/O machismo/O ./O
A/O mixture/O that/O immediately/O gained/O traction/O with/O vast/O Latino/O audiences/O ,/O mostly/O prepubescent/O and/O adolescents/O males/O ./O
Latino/O Fant¶mas/PERSON also/O was/O a/O millionaire/O ,/O owning/O several/O corporations/O under/O assumed/O identities/O ,/O had/O secret/O headquarters/O outside/O Paris/LOCATION ,/O and/O was/O assisted/O by/O several/O secret/O agents/O ,/O including/O the/O 12/O ``/O Zodiac/O Girls/O ''/O ,/O beautiful/O women/O who/O assisted/O him/O personally/O and/O dressed/O provocatively/O ,/O known/O only/O by/O their/O codenames/O -/O the/O signs/O of/O the/O zodiac/O ./O
The/O attractive/O female/O element/O was/O another/O concession/O to/O Latin/O American/O audiences/O familiar/O with/O beautiful/O women/O as/O part/O of/O male-dominated/O environments/O playing/O key/O roles/O without/O hiding/O their/O femininity/O and/O preceding/O Charlie/PERSON 's/O Angels/O by/O decades/O ./O
Although/O cancelled/O years/O ago/O -LRB-/O Novaro/PERSON folded/O in/O 1985/O ,/O and/O a/O character/O revival/O by/O rival/O Grupo/ORGANIZATION Editorial/ORGANIZATION Vid/ORGANIZATION in/O Mexico/LOCATION in/O the/O 1990s/O did/O not/O last/O long/O -RRB-/O ,/O it/O is/O from/O this/O Mexican/O comic/O that/O the/O character/O is/O best/O known/O in/O both/O Central/LOCATION America/LOCATION and/O South/LOCATION America/LOCATION ./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON continues/O to/O be/O one/O of/O Latin/LOCATION America/LOCATION 's/O favorite/O comic/O characters/O ./O
For/O more/O information/O on/O this/O version/O of/O the/O character/O check/O the/O link/O to/O the/O Fantomas/O Lives/O website/O below/O ./O
A/O short/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O story/O by/O Paul/PERSON Kupperberg/PERSON and/O Roy/PERSON Mann/PERSON appeared/O in/O ''/O Captain/O Action/O Comics/O ''/O No./O 1/O ,/O published/O in/O 2009/O by/O Moonstone/ORGANIZATION Books/ORGANIZATION ./O
The/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O novels/O and/O the/O subsequent/O films/O were/O highly/O regarded/O by/O the/O French/O avant-garde/O of/O the/O day/O ,/O particularly/O by/O the/O surrealists/O ./O
Blaise/PERSON Cendrars/PERSON called/O the/O series/O ``/O the/O modern/O Aeneid/O ''/O ;/O Guillaume/PERSON Apollinaire/PERSON said/O that/O ``/O from/O the/O imaginative/O standpoint/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O is/O one/O of/O the/O richest/O works/O that/O exist/O ./O ''/O
The/O painter/O RenÚ/PERSON Magritte/PERSON and/O the/O surrealist/O poet/O and/O novelist/O Robert/PERSON Desnos/PERSON both/O produced/O works/O alluding/O to/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
The/O movies/O were/O also/O very/O popular/O in/O the/O Soviet/LOCATION Union/LOCATION ./O
After/O their/O success/O Fant¶mas/PERSON had/O a/O short/O appearance/O in/O two/O popular/O Soviet/O comedies/O :/O ``/O Seven/O Old/O Men/O and/O One/O Girl/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1968/O ,/O directed/O by/O E./PERSON Karelov/PERSON -RRB-/O and/O ``/O Old/O Men/O Bandits/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1971/O ,/O directed/O by/O E./PERSON Ryazanov/PERSON -RRB-/O ./O
In/O 2007/O ,/O Russian/O author/O Andrey/PERSON Shary/PERSON published/O the/O book/O ''/O Sign/O F/O :/O Fantomas/O in/O Books/O and/O on/O the/O Screen/O ''/O ,/O dealing/O in/O particular/O with/O this/O phenomenon/O ./O
*/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O may/O well/O have/O been/O influenced/O by/O its/O less/O well/O remembered/O predecessor/O ,/O ''/O Zigomar/O ''/O ,/O the/O creation/O of/O LÚon/PERSON Sazie/PERSON ,/O which/O first/O appeared/O as/O a/O serial/O in/O ''/O Le/O Matin/O ''/O in/O 1909/O ,/O then/O as/O a/O pulp/O magazine/O -LRB-/O 28/O issues/O -RRB-/O in/O 1913/O ,/O and/O again/O in/O ''/O Zigomar/O contre/O Zigomar/O ''/O for/O eight/O more/O issues/O in/O 1924/O ./O
*/O In/O France/LOCATION alone/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON spawned/O numerous/O imitators/O ./O
Among/O those/O are/O Arnould/PERSON Galopin/PERSON 's/O ''/O Tenebras/O ''/O ,/O Gaston/PERSON RenÚ/PERSON 's/O ''/O Masque/O Rouge/O ''/O ,/O Arthur/PERSON BernÞde/PERSON 's/O ''/O BelphÚgor/O -LRB-/O novel/O -RRB-/O |/O BelphÚgor/O ''/O ,/O R./PERSON Collard/PERSON 's/O ''/O Demonax/O ''/O and/O Marcel/PERSON Allain/PERSON 's/O own/O ''/O Tigris/O ''/O ,/O ''/O Fatala/O ''/O ,/O ''/O Miss/O Teria/O ''/O and/O ''/O Ferocias/O ''/O ./O
*/O The/O 1915/O adventure/O film/O ''/O Filibus/O ''/O was/O probably/O inspired/O largely/O by/O the/O popularity/O of/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O ,/O although/O the/O film/O 's/O title/O character/O ,/O a/O female/O air/O pirate/O ,/O strongly/O resembles/O ArsÞne/ORGANIZATION Lupin/ORGANIZATION ./O
*/O After/O the/O success/O of/O the/O first/O Fant¶mas/O -LRB-/O 1913/O serial/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O film/O serial/O directed/O by/O Louis/PERSON Feuillade/PERSON ,/O Gaumont/PERSON produced/O another/O serial/O directed/O by/O Feuillade/PERSON in/O the/O same/O style/O ,/O ''/O Les/O Vampires/O ''/O ,/O about/O a/O gang/O of/O criminals/O ./O
As/O Feuillade/PERSON had/O been/O criticized/O for/O glorifying/O outlaws/O ,/O his/O next/O serial/O for/O Gaumont/PERSON ,/O ''/O Judex/O ''/O ,/O starred/O this/O time/O a/O positive/O hero/O ,/O a/O mysterious/O avenger/O conceived/O as/O an/O honest/O version/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
Judex/PERSON was/O himself/O featured/O in/O various/O adaptations/O ,/O sequels/O and/O remakes/O ./O
The/O original/O ''/O Judex/O ''/O serial/O was/O released/O in/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION and/O appears/O to/O have/O been/O an/O inspiration/O for/O the/O American/O pulp/O character/O The/O Shadow/O ,/O who/O was/O himself/O an/O inspiration/O for/O Batman.Xavier/PERSON Fournier/PERSON ,/O ''/O Super-hÚros/O :/O une/O histoire/O franþaise/O ''/O ,/O Huginn/PERSON Muninn/PERSON ,/O 2014/O ,/O p./O 69-73/O */O Fant¶mas/O has/O appeared/O in/O an/O unauthorized/O fashion/O in/O two/O French/O stage/O plays/O :/O ''/O Nick/PERSON Carter/PERSON vs./O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O 1910/O -RRB-/O by/O Alexandre/PERSON Bisson/PERSON and/O Guillaume/PERSON Livet/PERSON -LRB-/O translated/O ,/O ISBN/O 978-1-934543-05-4/O -RRB-/O and/O ''/O Sherlock/PERSON Holmes/PERSON vs./O Fant¶mas/O ''/O -LRB-/O ''/O La/O Mort/O d'/O Herlock/O Sholmes/O ,/O ou/O Bandits/O en/O Habits/O Noirs/O ''/O ,/O 1914/O -RRB-/O by/O Pierre/PERSON de/PERSON Wattyne/PERSON and/O Yorril/PERSON Walter/PERSON -LRB-/O translated/O ,/O ISBN/O 978-1-934543-67-2/O -RRB-/O ./O
*/O A/O number/O of/O Italian/O dark/O villains/O of/O the/O 1960s/O were/O clearly/O influenced/O by/O Fant¶mas/PERSON ./O
Among/O the/O most/O famous/O are/O Diabolik/O ,/O Kriminal/O ,/O Killing/O ,/O and/O Satanik/O ./O
*/O The/O British/O film/O critic/O and/O writer/O Kim/PERSON Newman/PERSON has/O argued/O that/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O inspired/O the/O ''/O Pink/O Panther/O ''/O film/O series/O starring/O Peter/PERSON Sellers/PERSON ./O
In/O the/O initial/O 1963/O ''/O Pink/O Panther/O ''/O film/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON was/O transformed/O into/O Sir/O Charles/PERSON Lytton/PERSON -LRB-/O the/O Phantom/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O Inspector/O Juve/PERSON became/O Inspector/O Clouseau/O ./O
*/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O also/O has/O many/O plot/O points/O in/O common/O with/O the/O 1969/O Hong/LOCATION Kong/LOCATION movie/O ''/O Temptress/O of/O a/O Thousand/O Faces/O ''/O ./O
*/O Paperinik/O ,/O -LRB-/O Duck/O Avenger/O -RRB-/O alter-ego/O of/O Donald/PERSON Duck/PERSON created/O by/O Guido/PERSON Martina/PERSON and/O Giovan/PERSON Battista/PERSON Carpi/PERSON in/O 1969/O ,/O is/O partly/O based/O on/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
His/O predecessor/O ,/O Fantomius/PERSON ,/O -LRB-/O Fantomallard/O -RRB-/O was/O obviously/O also/O named/O after/O Fant¶mas/PERSON ./O
In/O France/LOCATION the/O character/O is/O known/O as/O Fantomiald/ORGANIZATION ;/O in/O Germany/LOCATION as/O Phantomias/ORGANIZATION ;/O in/O Greek/O as/O Phantom/O Duck/O and/O in/O Spain/LOCATION as/O Patomas/O ./O
*/O ''/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O inspired/O Julio/PERSON Cortßzar/PERSON 's/O 1975/O novella/O ''/O Fantomas/O contra/O los/O vampiros/O multinacionales/O ''/O ./O
*/O A/O character/O in/O the/O Doctor/O Who/O novel/O The/O Man/O in/O the/O Velvet/O Mask/O -LRB-/O 1996/O -RRB-/O is/O named/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
*/O ''/O Fantomas/O ''/O was/O the/O inspiration/O for/O the/O character/O Mr./O Ixnay/PERSON ,/O who/O appears/O in/O ''/O The/O Chuckling/O Whatsit/O ''/O ,/O a/O 1997/O graphic/O novel/O by/O writer/artist/O Richard/PERSON Sala/PERSON ,/O creator/O of/O ''/O Invisible/O Hands/O ''/O ,/O an/O animated/O homage/O to/O old-fashioned/O mystery/O thrillers/O which/O aired/O on/O MTV/ORGANIZATION ./O
*/O In/O 1999/O ,/O former/O Faith/O No/O More/O singer/O Mike/PERSON Patton/PERSON named/O his/O metal/O group/O ''/O Fant¶mas/PERSON -LRB-/O band/O -RRB-/O |/O Fant¶mas/O ''/O after/O the/O fictional/O character/O ./O
*/O There/O is/O a/O Marvel/ORGANIZATION Comics/ORGANIZATION character/O named/O Fantomex/O ,/O first/O appearing/O in/O August/O 2002/O ./O
He/O was/O created/O by/O Grant/PERSON Morrison/PERSON and/O Igor/PERSON Kordey/PERSON for/O the/O title/O ''/O New/O X-Men/O ''/O ./O
*/O In/O one/O of/O the/O The/O New/O Traveller/O 's/O Almanac/O |/O back-story/O sections/O of/O the/O graphic/O novel/O ''/O The/O League/O of/O Extraordinary/O Gentlemen/O ,/O Volume/O II/O ''/O ,/O Fant¶mas/PERSON is/O described/O as/O being/O a/O member/O of/O ``/O Les/O Hommes/O MystÚrieux/O ''/O ,/O the/O French/O counterpart/O of/O the/O League/O ,/O alongside/O ArsÞne/O Lupin/O ,/O the/O sky-pirate/O Robur/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O the/O Nyctalope/O ./O
In/O the/O follow-up/O ,/O ''/O The/O League/O of/O Extraordinary/O Gentlemen/O :/O Black/O Dossier/O ''/O ,/O the/O League/O 's/O encounter/O with/O Les/ORGANIZATION Hommes/ORGANIZATION is/O halted/O once/O Fant¶mas/ORGANIZATION detonates/O a/O bomb/O which/O destroys/O the/O Opera/O Garnier/PERSON ,/O after/O saying/O in/O unaccented/O English/O ,/O ``/O I/O win/O ''/O ./O
*/O The/O character/O of/O Spectrobert/LOCATION in/O Gahan/PERSON Wilson/PERSON 's/O book/O ''/O Everybody/O 's/O Favorite/O Duck/O ''/O is/O a/O direct/O parody/O of/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
*/O Fant¶mas/O is/O a/O partial/O inspiration/O for/O the/O character/O of/O Phantom/O Limb/O on/O the/O Adult/O Swim/O cartoon/O ''/O The/O Venture/O Bros./O ''/O His/O last/O name/O ,/O in/O fact/O ,/O is/O Fant¶mas/O ./O
A/O picture/O similar/O in/O appearance/O to/O the/O masked/O villain/O can/O be/O seen/O hanging/O on/O the/O wall/O of/O his/O office/O at/O State/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION in/O ``/O The/O Invisible/O Hand/O of/O Fate/O ''/O ./O
It/O is/O revealed/O that/O Phantom/O Limb/O is/O actually/O the/O grandson/O of/O the/O famous/O criminal/O ./O
Fant¶mas/PERSON himself/O briefly/O appears/O in/O the/O series/O during/O a/O flashback/O in/O the/O season/O 3/O episode/O ``/O ORB/O ''/O as/O one/O of/O the/O original/O members/O of/O the/O Guild/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Calamitous/ORGANIZATION Intent/ORGANIZATION ./O
*/O Fant¶mas/O has/O a/O German/O cousin/O in/O the/O person/O of/O the/O -LRB-/O supposedly/O British/O -RRB-/O Lord/O Lister/PERSON ./O
*/O In/O the/O story/O ``/O Fant¶mville/O ''/O by/O Nick/PERSON Campbell/PERSON ,/O in/O the/O book/O ''/O Wildthyme/O in/O Purple/O ''/O ,/O Fantomas/O meets/O the/O time/O traveller/O Iris/PERSON Wildthyme/PERSON ./O
*/O In/O the/O film/O adaptation/O of/O Alan/PERSON Moore/PERSON and/O Kevin/PERSON O'Neill/PERSON -LRB-/O comics/O -RRB-/O |/O Kevin/PERSON O'Neill/PERSON 's/O ''/O The/O League/O of/O Extraordinary/O Gentlemen/O ''/O ,/O the/O Fantom/PERSON -LRB-/O a/O character/O resembling/O the/O title/O character/O from/O ''/O The/O Phantom/O of/O the/O Opera/O ''/O -RRB-/O owes/O more/O than/O a/O little/O to/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION ,/O although/O he/O is/O ultimately/O revealed/O to/O be/O M/O ,/O who/O in/O turn/O is/O revealed/O to/O be/O Professor/O Moriarty/PERSON ./O
The/O character/O is/O commonly/O associated/O with/O the/O X-Men/O titles/O ./O
Fantomex/O first/O appeared/O in/O ''/O X-Men/O :/O Legacy/O #New/O X-Men/O |/O New/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 128/O -LRB-/O August/O ,/O 2002/O -RRB-/O and/O was/O created/O by/O Grant/PERSON Morrison/PERSON and/O Igor/PERSON Kordey/PERSON ./O
Initially/O introduced/O as/O a/O character/O similar/O to/O Fant¶mas/LOCATION and/O Diabolik/PERSON ,/O he/O is/O later/O revealed/O to/O be/O an/O escaped/O experiment/O from/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O Program/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON resembles/O the/O titular/O character/O of/O the/O Italian/O comic/O book/O ''/O Diabolik/O ''/O ,/O whose/O film/O adaptation/O was/O released/O as/O ''/O Danger/O :/O Diabolik/O ''/O ,/O Diabolik/PERSON 's/O lover/O being/O named/O Eva/PERSON ./O
The/O character/O of/O Diabolik/O is/O loosely/O based/O on/O the/O character/O Fant¶mas/O ,/O the/O subject/O of/O a/O series/O of/O early-20th/O century/O French/O detective/O thrillers/O and/O a/O popular/O Mexican/O comic/O book/O adaptation/O ,/O whose/O name/O is/O more/O directly/O reflected/O in/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION 's/O own/O name./O ,/O Comic/ORGANIZATION Book/ORGANIZATION Resources/ORGANIZATION Fantomex/ORGANIZATION 's/O name/O ,/O Jean-Phillipe/PERSON ,/O is/O a/O reference/O to/O actor/O John/PERSON Phillip/PERSON Law/PERSON ,/O star/O of/O ``/O Danger/O :/O Diabolik/O ''/O ./O
In/O addition/O ,/O his/O Weapon/O X/O designation/O -/O ``/O Weapon/O XIII/O ''/O -/O is/O a/O reference/O to/O the/O secret/O agent/O protagonist/O of/O the/O Franco-Belgian/O comic/O ''/O XIII/O ''/O ./O
After/O Morrison/PERSON 's/O run/O ,/O the/O character/O made/O sporadic/O appearances/O in/O ''/O Weapon/O X/O ''/O #/O 23-25/O ,/O ''/O Mystique/O ''/O #/O 20-21/O ,/O 24/O ,/O the/O ''/O Dark/O Reign/O :/O The/O List-Wolverine/O ''/O one-shot/O and/O in/O ''/O Uncanny/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 515-522/O during/O the/O ``/O Nation/O X/O ''/O storyline/O before/O becoming/O a/O founding/O member/O of/O a/O new/O covert/O X-Force/O as/O seen/O in/O the/O monthly/O ''/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O series/O ./O
In/O July/O 2013/O ,/O Marvel/O announced/O the/O character/O 's/O first/O solo/O series/O ,/O ''/O Fantomex/O MAX/O ''/O ,/O written/O by/O Andrew/PERSON Hope/PERSON ,/O and/O illustrated/O by/O Shawn/PERSON Crystal/PERSON ./O
The/O series/O does/O not/O take/O place/O in/O current/O Marvel/O continuity/O ,/O and/O the/O character/O is/O not/O affiliated/O with/O any/O other/O Marvel/O characters/O ./O
In/O this/O series/O ,/O the/O character/O of/O Fantomex/O is/O a/O more/O literal/O take/O on/O the/O Diabolik/O character/O ,/O with/O a/O storyline/O less/O influenced/O by/O traditional/O superhero/O plots/O ,/O skewing/O more/O towards/O the/O concepts/O of/O intrigue/O and/O James/PERSON Bond-tinged/PERSON adventure/O ./O
Issue/O #/O 1/O debuted/O on/O October/O 2/O ,/O 2013/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON was/O created/O by/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O Program/O to/O serve/O as/O a/O Sentinels/O -LRB-/O comics/O -RRB-/O |/O super-sentinel/O against/O Earth/LOCATION 's/O mutant/O population/O ./O
Weapon/O Plus/O created/O a/O population/O of/O Techno-organic/O material/O |/O technorganic/O organisms/O whose/O living/O tissue/O was/O fused/O with/O Sentinel/O nanotechnology/O at/O the/O cellular/O level/O ./O
His/O mother/O ,/O a/O member/O of/O this/O race/O ,/O became/O pregnant/O when/O she/O was/O fertilized/O with/O nanomachines/O ,/O resulting/O in/O the/O birth/O of/O Fantomex/LOCATION ./O
Like/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O people/O ,/O he/O was/O born/O and/O raised/O in/O Weapon/O Plus/O #The/O World/O |/O the/O World/O ,/O a/O man-made/O environment/O designed/O to/O create/O super-sentinels/O ,/O media-friendly/O mutant-hunters/O modeled/O after/O Saturday/O morning/O cartoons/O ./O
Although/O his/O nationality/O is/O technically/O British/O as/O the/O World/O was/O located/O in/O England/LOCATION ,/O Fantomex/PERSON claims/O he/O was/O raised/O in/O a/O virtual/O France/LOCATION with/O imperfect/O programming/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O #/O 13/O He/O 's/O developed/O a/O French/O sense/O of/O identity/O and/O persona/O ;/O whereas/O his/O experiment/O designation/O at/O the/O World/O facility/O was/O ``/O Charlie/O Cluster-7/O ''/O ,/O he/O usually/O goes/O by/O the/O name/O ``/O Jean-Phillipe/PERSON ''/O ./O
During/O his/O first/O appearance/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON seeks/O a/O safe/O haven/O at/O the/O X-Corporation/O in/O Paris/LOCATION while/O fleeing/O from/O authorities/O ./O
He/O claims/O to/O be/O a/O mutant/O thief/O with/O the/O ill-defined/O power/O of/O misdirection/O ./O
Bleeding/O profusely/O from/O bullet/O wounds/O ,/O he/O asks/O for/O asylum/O ,/O which/O Professor/O X/O grants/O him/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON explains/O to/O Professor/PERSON X/PERSON and/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON that/O he/O is/O being/O hunted/O because/O he/O is/O one/O of/O the/O most/O wanted/O thieves/O in/O Europe/LOCATION ./O
Neither/O Professor/O X/O nor/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON are/O able/O to/O verify/O his/O claims/O due/O to/O his/O ceramic/O mask/O ,/O a/O device/O that/O blocks/O their/O mental/O probes/O ./O
However/O ,/O they/O agree/O to/O aid/O him/O ,/O and/O after/O escaping/O the/O soldiers/O who/O surround/O the/O building/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON uses/O his/O ship/O E.V.A./O to/O take/O Professor/PERSON X/PERSON and/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON to/O his/O home/O in/O France/LOCATION ./O
While/O there/O ,/O he/O introduces/O them/O to/O his/O mother/O and/O continues/O to/O describe/O his/O success/O as/O a/O thief/O ./O
In/O fact/O ,/O he/O tells/O the/O two/O that/O he/O has/O stolen/O sensitive/O information/O about/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O project/O while/O in/O the/O Chunnel/O ,/O and/O offers/O to/O sell/O it/O to/O Professor/O Xavier/PERSON for/O $/O 1/O billion/O ./O
After/O submitting/O his/O proposal/O ,/O he/O puts/O himself/O in/O a/O light/O hypnotic/O trance/O and/O removes/O the/O bullets/O that/O riddle/O his/O body/O ./O
Finished/O ,/O he/O asks/O Professor/PERSON X/PERSON and/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON to/O accompany/O him/O back/O to/O the/O Chunnel/O in/O an/O effort/O to/O destroy/O Weapon/O XII/O ./O
The/O three/O speed/O away/O in/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION ,/O leaving/O the/O house/O and/O elderly/O woman/O behind/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON then/O leads/O Professor/O Xavier/PERSON and/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON to/O the/O Chunnel/O disaster/O ./O
Packed/O full/O of/O people/O and/O animals/O that/O Weapon/ORGANIZATION XII/ORGANIZATION has/O turned/O into/O mindless/O slaves/O ,/O confusion/O runs/O rampant/O ./O
Knowing/O that/O those/O who/O have/O fallen/O prey/O to/O Weapon/O XII/O 's/O influence/O are/O lost/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON kills/O Darkstar/ORGANIZATION and/O all/O others/O who/O are/O mentally/O connected/O to/O the/O creature/O ./O
After/O Fantomex/O destroys/O Weapon/O XII/O by/O using/O a/O remote/O detonator/O ,/O it/O is/O noticed/O that/O there/O are/O two/O empty/O Weapon/O Plus/O transport/O tubes/O in/O the/O Chunnel/O :/O one/O that/O held/O the/O violent/O Weapon/O XII/O and/O another/O that/O held/O something/O called/O Weapon/O XIII/O ./O
After/O the/O battle/O ,/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION 's/O ceramic/O mask/O slips/O a/O bit/O and/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON uses/O her/O telepathy/O to/O deduce/O his/O true/O identity/O :/O Fantomex/O is/O actually/O Weapon/O XIII/O and/O had/O also/O been/O in/O transit/O in/O the/O Chunnel/O ./O
It/O was/O during/O the/O accident/O in/O the/O Chunnel/O that/O he/O escaped/O and/O was/O subsequently/O chased/O to/O the/O X-Corporation/O building/O ./O
He/O confesses/O to/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON that/O he/O is/O not/O the/O master/O thief/O that/O he/O had/O claimed/O ,/O but/O is/O now/O set/O out/O to/O earn/O that/O reputation/O ./O
He/O assures/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON that/O he/O refuses/O to/O be/O anyone/O 's/O soldier/O ,/O and/O as/O a/O result/O Jean/PERSON Grey/PERSON allows/O Fantomex/O to/O disappear/O into/O the/O Chunnel/O before/O the/O authorities/O arrive/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON later/O travels/O to/O Afghanistan/LOCATION in/O an/O attempt/O to/O steal/O a/O list/O of/O the/O world/O 's/O richest/O mutant/O slaver/O traders/O ,/O the/O names/O on/O which/O he/O intends/O to/O blackmail/O ./O
There/O he/O encounters/O an/O unconscious/O mutant/O known/O as/O Dust/O ,/O a/O former/O captive/O who/O unwittingly/O killed/O her/O captors/O by/O turning/O into/O a/O deadly/O sandstorm/O ./O
Upon/O his/O exit/O ,/O he/O encounters/O Wolverine/O ,/O leaving/O Dust/O in/O his/O care/O ./O ''/O
New/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 133/O Soon/O after/O ,/O Fantomex/O contacts/O Wolverine/PERSON and/O offers/O him/O information/O about/O his/O mysterious/O past/O if/O he/O helps/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION destroy/O Ultimaton/PERSON ,/O also/O known/O as/O Weapon/O XV/O ,/O the/O last/O creation/O of/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O Program/O ./O
Fantomex/O ,/O Wolverine/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O X-Men/O 's/O Cyclops/O travel/O to/O the/O World/O ,/O an/O artificial/O ,/O time-altering/O environment/O designed/O by/O Weapon/O Plus/O to/O quickly/O develop/O and/O evolve/O new/O generations/O of/O super-soldiers/O ./O
The/O three/O are/O defeated/O by/O Weapon/O XV/O -LRB-/O Ultimaton/LOCATION -RRB-/O ,/O who/O escapes/O by/O breaking/O through/O the/O barriers/O of/O the/O World/O and/O flying/O to/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O space/O station/O ./O
The/O team/O pursues/O their/O target/O in/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION ,/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION 's/O biological/O spacecraft/O ./O
Upon/O arriving/O at/O the/O space/O station/O Fantomex/O keeps/O his/O word/O by/O showing/O Wolverine/O the/O complete/O Weapon/O Plus/O database/O ./O
Shocked/O at/O learning/O the/O terrible/O details/O of/O his/O past/O -LRB-/O including/O his/O role/O in/O the/O slaughter/O of/O the/O entire/O population/O of/O Roanoke/LOCATION while/O under/O the/O influence/O of/O Weapon/O X/O -RRB-/O ,/O Wolverine/PERSON initiates/O the/O self-destruct/O sequence/O for/O the/O space/O station/O before/O catching/O and/O apparently/O killing/O Ultimaton/PERSON -LRB-/O who/O reappears/O later/O as/O a/O subordinate/O ''/O Ultimate/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 5/O -RRB-/O ./O
Fantomex/O and/O Cyclops/O escape/O the/O explosion/O in/O one/O of/O the/O station/O 's/O shuttles/O ./O ''/O
New/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 145/O Back/O on/O Earth/LOCATION ,/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION joins/O Cyclops/O and/O a/O group/O of/O X-Men/O students/O in/O their/O fight/O against/O Xorn/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O taken/O the/O identity/O of/O Magneto/PERSON ./O
He/O had/O gathered/O a/O new/O Brotherhood/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Mutants/ORGANIZATION and/O had/O taken/O over/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O
With/O the/O aid/O of/O Beak/O ,/O Fantomex/O ,/O and/O the/O others/O were/O able/O to/O break/O into/O Xorn/PERSON 's/O skyscraper/O headquarters/O and/O bring/O him/O down/O ./O ''/O
New/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 150/O Later/O on/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON tries/O to/O track/O down/O John/PERSON Sublime/PERSON ,/O the/O director/O of/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O program/O ./O
However/O ,/O upon/O examining/O his/O empty/O grave/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON finds/O a/O note/O reading/O ,/O ``/O Roanoke/O ./O ''/O ''/O
Weapon/O X/O ''/O #/O 23/O He/O locates/O the/O secret/O facility/O of/O the/O splinter/O program/O Weapon/O X/O and/O finds/O it/O abandoned/O except/O for/O Agent/O Zero/O ./O
The/O pair/O reluctantly/O joins/O forces/O and/O travels/O to/O the/O site/O of/O Roanoke/LOCATION ,/O a/O town/O whose/O inhabitants/O were/O slaughtered/O after/O Weapon/O X/O unleashed/O a/O brainwashed/O Wolverine/O on/O them/O years/O earlier/O ./O
There/O ,/O the/O three/O finally/O encounter/O Sublime/O but/O are/O opposed/O by/O his/O U-Men/O -LRB-/O comics/O -RRB-/O |/O U-Men/O and/O forced/O to/O flee/O against/O overwhelming/O odds/O ./O
In/O an/O attempt/O to/O escape/O in/O E.V.A./O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON is/O shot/O down/O and/O left/O for/O dead/O ./O ''/O
Weapon/O X/O ''/O #/O 25/O However/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON manages/O to/O survive/O and/O some/O time/O later/O is/O contacted/O by/O the/O diminutive/O mutant/O Shortpack/PERSON who/O seeks/O his/O help/O in/O assassinating/O mutant/O arms/O dealer/O Steinbeck/PERSON ,/O also/O known/O as/O the/O Quiet/O Man/O ,/O in/O revenge/O for/O his/O killing/O of/O an/O agent/O under/O Shortpack/PERSON 's/O care/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON refuses/O ,/O not/O wanting/O to/O become/O responsible/O for/O allowing/O the/O good-natured/O Shortpack/O to/O become/O a/O killer/O ./O
Shortpack/O is/O captured/O by/O Steinbeck/PERSON soon/O after/O ,/O and/O whilst/O investigating/O his/O disappearance/O the/O shapechanging/O mutant/O Mystique/O ,/O a/O double/O agent/O for/O both/O Xavier/PERSON and/O Steinbeck/PERSON 's/O ally/O Shepard/PERSON ,/O learns/O of/O his/O meeting/O with/O Fantomex/PERSON ./O
Though/O despising/O him/O after/O a/O past/O encounter/O in/O Madagascar/LOCATION ,/O Mystique/O finds/O Fantomex/PERSON in/O Monte/LOCATION Carlo/LOCATION ,/O once/O again/O operating/O under/O the/O pretense/O of/O being/O a/O mutant/O thief/O ,/O and/O learns/O of/O Shortpack/PERSON 's/O plan/O ./O ''/O
Mystique/O ''/O #/O 20/O As/O she/O leaves/O to/O rescue/O him/O ,/O Fantomex/O follows/O and/O uncovers/O her/O intent/O to/O assassinate/O Xavier/PERSON ./O
In/O exchange/O for/O his/O silence/O ,/O Fantomex/O bids/O Mystique/O perform/O a/O heist/O for/O him/O ./O
After/O she/O returns/O with/O the/O stolen/O goods/O -LRB-/O a/O vintage/O Spider-Man/O costume/O -RRB-/O ,/O Mystique/O infects/O both/O Fantomex/O and/O E.V.A./O with/O a/O techno-organic/O virus/O ,/O seemingly/O killing/O them/O both/O to/O keep/O her/O plan/O secret/O ./O ''/O
Mystique/O ''/O #/O 21/O However/O ,/O it/O was/O all/O a/O ruse/O as/O Mystique/PERSON knew/O she/O was/O being/O monitored/O by/O Shepard/PERSON ./O
Fantomex/O later/O resurfaces/O and/O helps/O Mystique/O capture/O Shepard/PERSON ,/O giving/O her/O access/O to/O Steinbeck/PERSON whom/O she/O finally/O defeats/O ./O ''/O
Mystique/O ''/O #/O 24/O During/O his/O tenure/O as/O leader/O of/O HAMMER/O ,/O Norman/PERSON Osborn/PERSON tries/O to/O take/O control/O of/O the/O World/O and/O the/O Weapon/O Plus/O creations/O ./O
Wolverine/PERSON and/O Noh-Varr/PERSON head/O to/O the/O World/O to/O try/O to/O stop/O Norman/PERSON Osborn/PERSON but/O are/O soon/O attacked/O by/O a/O large/O army/O of/O Weapon/O Plus/O creations/O infected/O by/O Allgod/PERSON -LRB-/O Weapon/O XVI/O -RRB-/O ,/O the/O living/O religion/O ./O
Noh-Varr/O is/O rescued/O by/O Fantomex/PERSON -LRB-/O who/O has/O apparently/O spent/O all/O the/O time/O since/O his/O last/O appearance/O ``/O stealing/O things/O mostly/O ''/O and/O admits/O he/O should/O have/O kept/O an/O eye/O on/O the/O World/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O the/O two/O of/O them/O make/O their/O way/O to/O the/O World/ORGANIZATION 's/O brain/O -LRB-/O now/O a/O sentient/O being/O -RRB-/O where/O they/O are/O confronted/O by/O the/O Allgod/O drones/O ,/O Wolverine/PERSON included/O ./O
Fantomex/O is/O not/O affected/O by/O Allgod/PERSON because/O nanites/O in/O his/O neocortex/O render/O him/O incapable/O of/O believing/O in/O anything/O greater/O than/O himself/O ./O
Noh-Varr/O is/O able/O to/O disarm/O Allgod/PERSON by/O kissing/O the/O World/O 's/O brain/O ,/O thus/O showing/O it/O some/O compassion/O ,/O and/O disabling/O Allgod/PERSON ./O
Immediately/O after/O this/O ,/O the/O three/O of/O them/O defeat/O Osborn/PERSON 's/O invading/O army/O of/O Deathlok/LOCATION prototypes/O ./O
Fantomex/O then/O uses/O a/O shrink-ray/O he/O reportedly/O stole/O from/O Doctor/O Doom/O to/O shrink/O the/O World/O and/O take/O it/O for/O his/O own/O ./O ''/O
Dark/O Reign/O :/O The/O List-Wolverine/O ''/O Soon/O afterwards/O Fantomex/O is/O hired/O by/O a/O young/O mutant/O boy/O to/O hunt/O a/O rogue/O Predator/O X/O stalking/O mutants/O beneath/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 519/O After/O dealing/O with/O the/O Predator/O X/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON and/O E.V.A./O run/O into/O Wolverine/O ,/O Psylocke/O ,/O and/O Colossus/O ,/O who/O ask/O for/O his/O help/O to/O defeat/O the/O creators/O of/O the/O Predator/O X./PERSON Fantomex/PERSON initially/O turns/O their/O request/O down/O ,/O but/O is/O later/O convinced/O by/O the/O same/O young/O boy/O he/O helped/O to/O help/O the/O X-Men/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON saves/O the/O team/O from/O a/O group/O of/O John/PERSON Sublime/PERSON 's/O associates/O and/O later/O takes/O them/O home/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 521/O Fantomex/O remains/O with/O the/O X-Men/O on/O Utopia/O and/O is/O later/O seen/O in/O San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION fighting/O alongside/O the/O X-Men/O against/O Bastion/O -LRB-/O comics/O -RRB-/O |/O Bastion/O 's/O army/O of/O Nimrod/O sentinels/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 525/O Once/O the/O battle/O is/O over/O ,/O he/O 's/O shown/O to/O have/O secretly/O joined/O a/O new/O iteration/O of/O X-Force/O ,/O alongside/O Wolverine/O ,/O Archangel/O ,/O Psylocke/O ,/O and/O Deadpool/O ./O ''/O
X-Men/O :/O Second/O Coming/O ''/O #/O 2/O in/O ''/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 12/O :/O ``/O Dark/O Angel/O Saga/O ,/O Chapter/O 2/O :/O Interruption/O ''/O -LRB-/O art/O by/O Chris/PERSON Stevens/PERSON -RRB-/O The/O first/O mission/O of/O the/O new/O team/O is/O an/O assassination/O job/O to/O kill/O Apocalypse/O ,/O reborn/O in/O the/O form/O of/O a/O child/O and/O being/O indoctrinated/O by/O Clan/PERSON Akkaba/PERSON on/O their/O Moon/O base/O ./O
After/O defeating/O Apocalypse/O 's/O Final/O Horsemen/O and/O getting/O to/O the/O young/O Apocalypse/O ,/O no/O one/O on/O the/O team/O can/O summon/O up/O the/O courage/O to/O kill/O a/O child/O ./O
When/O the/O group/O resigns/O to/O bring/O the/O child/O back/O with/O them/O and/O to/O reeducate/O him/O ,/O Fantomex/O fires/O a/O shot/O in/O the/O child/O 's/O head/O ,/O apparently/O killing/O him/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 4/O Soon/O afterwards/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON realizes/O a/O presence/O calling/O itself/O Weapon/ORGANIZATION Infinity/ORGANIZATION has/O started/O manipulating/O the/O timestream/O within/O the/O World/O ./O
After/O a/O battle/O against/O Weapon/ORGANIZATION Infinity/ORGANIZATION -LRB-/O actually/O the/O transforming/O of/O all/O future/O heroes/O into/O time-travelling/O Deathlok-type/O cyborgs/O ''/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O #/O 5/O -RRB-/O ,/O it/O is/O revealed/O that/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION has/O actually/O cloned/O the/O Apocalypse/O child/O in/O order/O to/O see/O if/O the/O boy/O could/O become/O a/O hero/O if/O raised/O as/O a/O good/O man/O in/O a/O virtual/O environment/O deep/O within/O the/O World/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 19/O Fantomex/O is/O later/O abducted/O by/O Captain/O Britain/LOCATION who/O brands/O him/O a/O dimensional/O threat/O and/O take/O him/O to/O Otherworld/O ,/O where/O an/O interdimensional/O court/O sentences/O him/O to/O erasure/O from/O existence/O itself/O ./O
He/O is/O rescued/O by/O his/O teammate/O Psylocke/PERSON ,/O who/O turns/O against/O her/O brothers/O ./O
Together/O they/O encounter/O the/O Skinless/O Man/O and/O rejoin/O their/O teammates/O to/O defeat/O The/O Goat/O ,/O a/O corrupted/O future/O incarnation/O of/O Psylocke/O and/O Captain/O Britain/LOCATION 's/O older/O brother/O Jamie/PERSON Braddock/PERSON ,/O who/O attempted/O to/O consume/O the/O multiverse/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 20/O -/O 24/O When/O Psylocke/O is/O captured/O by/O the/O newly/O reformed/O Brotherhood/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Evil/ORGANIZATION Mutants/ORGANIZATION ,/O Fantomex/PERSON sacrifices/O himself/O to/O save/O her/O ./O
He/O is/O captured/O and/O killed/O when/O the/O Skinless/O Man/O cuts/O out/O his/O heart/O ./O
With/O his/O connection/O to/O E.V.A/O severed/O ,/O she/O believes/O herself/O dying/O as/O well/O ./O
She/O survives/O ,/O however/O ,/O and/O evolves/O into/O a/O humanoid/O form/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 27/O After/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O disbands/O ,/O E.V.A./O attempts/O to/O clone/O Fantomex/PERSON back/O to/O life/O ,/O but/O due/O to/O his/O three/O brains/O ,/O an/O error/O occurs/O and/O three/O different/O bodies/O are/O grown/O for/O each/O personality/O :/O the/O evil/O brain/O becomes/O ``/O Weapon/O XIII/O ''/O -LRB-/O originally/O referred/O to/O as/O ``/O Jean-Phillippe/PERSON ''/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O wears/O a/O costume/O with/O inverted/O colors/O ;/O the/O noble/O brain/O becomes/O ``/O Cluster/O ''/O ,/O a/O female/O version/O of/O Fantomex/O ;/O and/O the/O mischievous/O one/O is/O restored/O to/O his/O proper/O body/O ,/O taking/O the/O name/O of/O ``/O Fantomex/O ''/O ./O
He/O goes/O on/O to/O continue/O his/O relationship/O with/O Psylocke/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 35/O Fantomex/ORGANIZATION and/O Cluster/O later/O hijack/O a/O plane/O -LRB-/O leaving/O the/O pilot/O drugged/O and/O the/O flight/O attendants/O bound/O and/O gagged/O -RRB-/O in/O order/O to/O find/O Psylocke/O and/O Storm/O ,/O but/O Weapon/O XIII/O follows/O and/O kidnaps/O Fantomex/O ./O
Cluster/O enlists/O the/O help/O of/O the/O new/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O -LRB-/O Puck/O ,/O Psylocke/O ,/O Spiral/O ,/O and/O Storm/O -RRB-/O to/O find/O Fantomex/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O -LRB-/O vol/O ./O
2/O -RRB-/O #/O 3/O Pyslocke/O and/O Cluster/O travel/O to/O Madripor/LOCATION to/O hunt/O Weapon/O XIII/O ./O
Weapon/O XIII/O uses/O his/O power/O of/O misdirection/O -LRB-/O which/O Fantomex/O and/O Cluster/O no/O longer/O possess/O -RRB-/O to/O confess/O his/O love/O to/O Psylocke/O ./O
She/O agrees/O to/O stay/O with/O him/O only/O if/O he/O allows/O her/O to/O kill/O Fantomex/PERSON ,/O who/O betrayed/O her/O during/O a/O heist/O at/O the/O Louvre/LOCATION ./O
During/O a/O heated/O battle/O she/O decides/O to/O free/O Fantomex/O and/O stun/O Weapon/O XIII/O ,/O stating/O that/O she/O is/O done/O with/O all/O three/O of/O them.Uncanny/O X-Force/O Vol/O ./O
2/O #/O 8/O Cable/O recruits/O Fantomex/PERSON as/O part/O of/O his/O new/O X-Force/O #Volume/O 4/O |/O X-Force/O team/O with/O the/O promise/O that/O he/O 'll/O help/O Fantomex/PERSON find/O Cluster/O and/O Weapon/O XIII/O ./O
He/O proves/O a/O questionable/O ally/O ,/O as/O he/O constantly/O bickers/O with/O Psylocke/PERSON and/O has/O a/O psychic/O sexual/O relations/O with/O Meme/PERSON ,/O who/O he/O really/O knows/O is/O actually/O Hope/PERSON Summers/PERSON -LRB-/O who/O Cable/O thinks/O is/O in/O a/O coma/O -RRB-/O ./O
He/O also/O kills/O new/O recruit/O List/O of/O Marvel/ORGANIZATION Comics/ORGANIZATION characters/O :/O F#/O ForgetMeNot/O |/O ForgetMeNot/O because/O ``/O he/O was/O bored/O ''/O ./O
X-Force/O Vol/O 4/O #/O 10/O The/O only/O concession/O that/O keeps/O Fantomex/PERSON in/O line/O is/O that/O he/O gets/O to/O kill/O Cable/O every/O night/O ,/O since/O Cable/ORGANIZATION 's/O body/O dies/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O day/O anyway/O and/O he/O has/O a/O clone/O ready/O to/O take/O his/O place/O the/O next/O day/O ./O
Eventually/O Hope/O hacks/O into/O his/O mind/O and/O unwittingly/O transfers/O the/O super-mutant/O genetic/O code/O from/O mutant/O arms/O trafficker/O Volga/LOCATION ./O
He/O then/O betrays/O the/O team/O ,/O but/O is/O shot/O in/O the/O head/O by/O Domino.X-Force/ORGANIZATION Vol/ORGANIZATION 4/O Issue/O #/O 11/O This/O is/O short-lived/O since/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION is/O able/O to/O reboot/O his/O brain/O using/O the/O super-mutant/O code/O and/O now/O Fantomex/PERSON has/O wings/O and/O god-like/O powers.X-Force/O Vol/O 4/O Issue/O #/O 12/O Initially/O ,/O he/O is/O tricked/O by/O Meme/Hope/PERSON Summers/PERSON into/O thinking/O he/O killed/O the/O team/O ,/O but/O once/O he/O learns/O the/O ruse/O he/O vows/O vengeance/O ./O
Fantomex/O is/O tricked/O again/O by/O Cable/O by/O agreeing/O to/O meet/O at/O various/O spy/O organization/O or/O organized/O crime/O locations/O for/O showdowns/O ,/O but/O X-Force/O never/O shows/O ;/O however/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON still/O destroys/O the/O base/O ,/O which/O ultimately/O helps/O X-Force/O 's/O missions/O ./O
Fantomex/PERSON eventually/O finds/O X-Force/O ,/O but/O is/O tricked/O by/O ForgetMeNot/PERSON into/O teleporting/O near/O Hope/PERSON Summers/PERSON ,/O who/O copies/O his/O super-powers/O ./O
X-Force/O Vol/O 4/O Issue/O #/O 14/O Instead/O of/O fighting/O him/O head-on/O ,/O Hope/O implants/O a/O thought/O into/O his/O mind/O that/O one/O can/O not/O be/O perfect/O ,/O unless/O you/O have/O a/O well/O rounded/O personality/O ,/O which/O includes/O inadequacies/O and/O insecurities/O ./O
Fantomex/O can/O not/O comprehend/O being/O perfect/O and/O imperfect/O ,/O so/O he/O has/O a/O mental/O breakdown/O ./O
Psylocke/O then/O uses/O her/O psychic/O blades/O to/O scramble/O his/O brain.X-Force/O Vol/O 4/O Issue/O #/O 15/O Fantomex/O can/O create/O extremely/O realistic/O illusions/O -LRB-/O he/O calls/O this/O ability/O ``/O misdirection/O ''/O -RRB-/O ./O
This/O ability/O is/O based/O on/O ``/O reality/O skewing/O ''/O ,/O rather/O than/O telepathy/O or/O holographic/O projection/O -LRB-/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O 14/O -RRB-/O ./O
Fantomex/O has/O an/O external/O nervous/O system/O referred/O to/O as/O E.V.A./O ./O
He/O has/O mentioned/O that/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION emerged/O from/O his/O mouth/O during/O his/O time/O in/O the/O World/O and/O developed/O into/O a/O techno-organic/O flying/O saucer-like/O vessel/O ./O
The/O relationship/O between/O E.V.A/O and/O Fantomex/LOCATION is/O symbiotic/O ,/O so/O if/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION experiences/O pain/O when/O she/O is/O not/O within/O Fantomex/PERSON ,/O he/O will/O feel/O it/O as/O well/O ./O
When/O E.V.A./PERSON is/O separated/O from/O his/O body/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON feels/O no/O pain/O and/O seems/O able/O to/O ignore/O most/O injuries/O ./O
Along/O with/O this/O symbiotic/O relationship/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON is/O linked/O to/O E.V.A./O via/O telepathy/O ./O
He/O can/O see/O through/O E.V.A./ORGANIZATION 's/O point/O of/O view/O and/O can/O take/O control/O of/O her/O movement/O ./O
However/O ,/O this/O requires/O concentration/O on/O the/O part/O of/O Fantomex/LOCATION ./O
Moreover/O ,/O E.V.A/O ,/O as/O a/O bio-mechanical/O being/O ,/O can/O reshape/O her/O body/O into/O a/O variety/O of/O forms/O ,/O fly/O herself/O ,/O and/O generate/O energy/O discharges/O to/O be/O used/O as/O weapons/O ./O
Fantomex/O contains/O three/O brains/O that/O used/O for/O parallel/O and/O independent/O thinking/O as/O well/O as/O nano-active/O blood/O ;/O the/O nanites/O in/O his/O brain/O prohibit/O him/O from/O believing/O in/O anything/O greater/O than/O himself/O ,/O such/O as/O gods/O or/O any/O supernatural/O beings/O ./O
He/O also/O maintains/O an/O internal/O back-up/O nervous/O system/O which/O can/O be/O engaged/O if/O E.V.A./O is/O damaged/O ./O
However/O ,/O this/O system/O is/O less/O complex/O than/O E.V.A./O and/O does/O not/O allow/O Fantomex/O to/O see/O colors/O ./O
He/O possesses/O enhanced/O strength/O ,/O speed/O ,/O agility/O ,/O dexterity/O ,/O durability/O ,/O reflexes/O ,/O coordination/O ,/O balance/O ,/O and/O endurance/O ./O
Fantomex/O is/O also/O capable/O of/O registering/O frequencies/O beyond/O the/O hearing/O range/O of/O normal/O humans/O ./O
He/O even/O once/O mentioned/O a/O healing/O factor/O ./O ''/O
Fear/O Itself/O :/O Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 2/O His/O three/O brains/O ,/O allow/O him/O to/O survive/O severe/O head/O wounds/O since/O his/O secondary/O brains/O can/O take/O over/O should/O one/O be/O destroyed/O ./O ''/O
Uncanny/O X-Force/O ''/O #/O 18/O Fantomex/O can/O also/O enter/O a/O trance/O state/O and/O perform/O crucial/O tasks/O such/O as/O performing/O surgery/O on/O himself/O ./O
In/O this/O state/O ,/O he/O can/O also/O recover/O faster/O while/O placed/O in/O water/O ./O
He/O can/O expertly/O read/O the/O body/O language/O of/O others/O in/O order/O to/O predict/O their/O attacks/O ./O
He/O is/O a/O very/O skilled/O hand-to-hand/O combatant/O and/O a/O master/O of/O stealth/O techniques/O ./O
His/O title/O in/O his/O birthplace/O ,/O the/O World/O ,/O was/O ``/O stealth-fighter/O ./O ''/O
Fantomex/O is/O a/O superb/O marksman/O ./O
He/O used/O to/O use/O special/O bullets/O covered/O in/O sentient/O mutant/O skin/O that/O never/O missed/O their/O target/O -LRB-/O designed/O by/O Sir/O James/PERSON Braddock/PERSON ,/O the/O father/O of/O Psylocke/O and/O Captain/O Britain/LOCATION -RRB-/O but/O he/O used/O his/O last/O of/O these/O against/O Archangel/O ./O
He/O carries/O a/O variety/O of/O guns/O and/O other/O weapons/O ./O
His/O mask/O incorporates/O telepathy-blocking/O ceramics/O ./O
These/O allow/O his/O mind/O to/O remain/O completely/O unreadable/O ,/O even/O facing/O the/O most/O powerful/O telepaths/O of/O the/O Marvel/O Universe/O -LRB-/O Professor/O X/O and/O the/O Shadow/O King/O among/O others/O -RRB-/O ./O
In/O one/O variant/O of/O the/O ''/O Days/O of/O Future/O Past/O ''/O timeline/O -LRB-/O titled/O ''/O Days/O of/O Future/O Now/O ''/O and/O depicted/O in/O Frank/PERSON Tieri/PERSON 's/O ''/O Weapon/O X/O ''/O series/O -RRB-/O ,/O Weapon/O X/O and/O the/O Sentinels/O are/O at/O war/O with/O Wolverine/PERSON 's/O X-Men/O and/O many/O other/O mutant/O groups/O ,/O including/O Excelsior/O and/O Gene/ORGANIZATION Nation/ORGANIZATION ./O
In/O this/O timeline/O ,/O Fantomex/PERSON becomes/O the/O host/O of/O Sublime/O and/O ,/O possessed/O by/O the/O sentient/O bacteria/O ,/O sabotages/O Wolverine/PERSON 's/O efforts/O to/O overthrow/O Weapon/O X./O ''/O Weapon/O X/O :/O Days/O of/O Future/O Now/O ''/O #/O 1/O ,/O 4-5/O In/O the/O ''/O Here/O Comes/O Tomorrow/O ''/O storyline/O ,/O set/O in/O an/O alternate/O timeline/O 150/O years/O in/O the/O future/O ,/O the/O entire/O world/O is/O ruled/O by/O Beast/O -LRB-/O possessed/O by/O Sublime/O -RRB-/O ./O
E.V.A./ORGANIZATION is/O a/O member/O of/O this/O era/O 's/O X-Men/O ,/O which/O includes/O Wolverine/O ,/O Tito/PERSON -LRB-/O Beak/O 's/O grandson/O -RRB-/O ,/O Tom/PERSON Skylark/PERSON and/O his/O Sentinel/O known/O as/O Rover/O ,/O Weapon/O XIV/O |/O Three-in-One/O -LRB-/O the/O Stepford/O Cuckoos/O -RRB-/O ,/O No-Girl/PERSON ,/O and/O a/O reformed/O Cassandra/PERSON Nova/PERSON as/O their/O leader/O ./O
E.V.A./ORGANIZATION has/O taken/O on/O a/O humanoid/O form/O and/O does/O not/O want/O to/O bond/O with/O anyone/O else/O 's/O nervous/O system/O after/O ``/O what/O happened/O to/O Fantomex/O ./O ''/O
Whatever/O happened/O to/O Fantomex/LOCATION is/O never/O explicitly/O explained/O in/O the/O storyline/O ,/O though/O it/O is/O strongly/O hinted/O that/O Beast/O 's/O U-Man/O follower/O ,/O Apollyon/O the/O Destroyer/O ,/O is/O actually/O Fantomex/O ./O ''/O
New/O X-Men/O ''/O #/O 151-154/O -LRB-/O 2005/O -RRB-/O Fantomex/O is/O depicted/O briefly/O in/O ''/O X-Men/O :/O The/O End/O ''/O as/O part/O of/O X-23/O 's/O dream/O induced/O by/O the/O Ladies/ORGANIZATION Mastermind/ORGANIZATION ,/O as/O she/O is/O stated/O to/O be/O in/O love/O with/O him/O in/O this/O reality/O ./O
In/O X-23/O 's/O dream/O ,/O they/O are/O shown/O together/O playing/O with/O a/O small/O daughter/O in/O their/O backyard/O ./O
*/O Fantomex/O makes/O a/O cameo/O appearance/O in/O Deadpool/LOCATION 's/O ending/O in/O ''/O Ultimate/O Marvel/O vs./O Capcom/ORGANIZATION 3/O ''/O ./O
*/O Fantomex/O appears/O as/O an/O unlockable/O character/O in/O ''/O Marvel/O :/O Avengers/O Alliance/O ''/O ./O
At/O first/O ,/O he/O could/O only/O be/O unlocked/O by/O completing/O the/O Season/O 6/O Adamantium/ORGANIZATION PVP/ORGANIZATION ,/O but/O he/O is/O now/O available/O normally/O ./O
*/O at/O Marvel.com/O */O */O ''/O `/O Marion/PERSON Anthony/PERSON D'Amico/PERSON ''/O '/O ,/O better/O known/O by/O his/O Mafia/O nickname/O ''/O ''/O `/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O '/O ''/O ,/O is/O a/O recurring/O character/O in/O the/O animated/O sitcom/O ''/O The/O Simpsons/O ''/O ./O
He/O is/O voiced/O by/O Joe/PERSON Mantegna/PERSON and/O first/O appeared/O in/O the/O third/O season/O episode/O ``/O Bart/O the/O Murderer/O ''/O ./O
Jean/PERSON ,/O Al/PERSON -LRB-/O 2003/O -RRB-/O ./O
Commentary/O for/O ``/O Bart/O the/O Murderer/O ''/O ,/O in/O ''/O The/O Simpsons/O :/O The/O Complete/O Third/O Season/O ''/O -LSB-/O DVD/O -RSB-/O ./O
20th/O Century/O Fox/PERSON ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON is/O a/O gangster/O and/O the/O underboss/O of/O the/O Springfield/ORGANIZATION Mafia/ORGANIZATION ./O
His/O henchmen/O include/O Legs/PERSON ,/O Louie/PERSON ,/O and/O Johnny/PERSON Tightlips/PERSON ,/O and/O he/O answers/O to/O Don/PERSON Vittorio/PERSON DiMaggio/PERSON ./O
The/O character/O somewhat/O resembles/O real-life/O mobster/O Anthony/PERSON Salerno/PERSON |/O ``/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O Salerno/PERSON ./O
While/O serving/O his/O terms/O ,/O real-life/O mobster/O ``/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O Salerno/PERSON died/O in/O a/O federal/O facility/O located/O in/O Springfield/LOCATION ,/O Missouri/LOCATION ./O
``/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O D'Amico/PERSON was/O behind/O several/O of/O Springfield/LOCATION 's/O criminal/O enterprises/O ./O
His/O rackets/O included/O illegal/O gambling/O ,/O cigarette/O smuggling/O ,/O and/O rum-running/O |/O bootlegging/O ./O
In/O ``/O The/O Twisted/O World/O of/O Marge/PERSON Simpson/PERSON ''/O ,/O Homer/O contracts/O with/O the/O mafia/O to/O drive/O out/O Marge/PERSON 's/O rival/O snack/O food/O distributors/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON took/O out/O a/O hit/O on/O Mayor/O Quimby/PERSON in/O ``/O Mayored/O to/O the/O Mob/O ''/O in/O retaliation/O for/O a/O raid/O on/O their/O rat/O milk/O facility/O ,/O which/O Quimby/PERSON opposed/O ,/O as/O they/O had/O promised/O him/O ``/O dog/O or/O higher/O ''/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON puts/O out/O a/O contract/O on/O Homer/O after/O his/O private/O security/O business/O interferes/O with/O the/O mob/O 's/O interests/O in/O ``/O Poppa/O 's/O Got/O a/O Brand/O New/O Badge/O ''/O ./O
Homer/O would/O have/O been/O executed/O gangland-style/O if/O not/O for/O Maggie/PERSON coming/O to/O the/O rescue/O with/O her/O rifle/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON 's/O son/O Michael/PERSON is/O first/O mentioned/O by/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON as/O he/O is/O talking/O to/O Marge/PERSON in/O ``/O The/O Seven-Beer/O Snitch/O ''/O ,/O saying/O she/O drove/O him/O home/O from/O school/O sometimes/O ./O
He/O is/O then/O properly/O introduced/O in/O the/O episode/O ``/O The/O Mook/O ,/O the/O Chef/O ,/O the/O Wife/O and/O Her/O Homer/O ''/O ./O
The/O episode/O also/O reveals/O that/O Fat/O Tony/PERSON 's/O wife/O ``/O was/O whacked/O by/O `/O natural/O causes/O '/O ./O ''/O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON and/O his/O associates/O meet/O in/O what/O is/O known/O as/O the/O ``/O Legitimate/ORGANIZATION Businessman/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Social/ORGANIZATION Club/ORGANIZATION ''/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON played/O the/O violin/O in/O ``/O Insane/O Clown/O Poppy/O ''/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON dies/O in/O the/O twenty-second/O season/O episode/O ``/O Donnie/O Fatso/O ''/O ,/O only/O to/O be/O replaced/O by/O his/O slimmer/O cousin/O ``/O Fit/O Tony/O ''/O ./O
By/O the/O end/O of/O that/O episode/O ,/O Fit/O Tony/PERSON has/O taken/O to/O eating/O as/O a/O way/O of/O dealing/O with/O the/O stress/O of/O assassination/O attempts/O ./O
His/O weight/O gain/O causes/O a/O change/O of/O nickname/O to/O ``/O Fit/O Fat/O Tony/PERSON ''/O and/O eventually/O ``/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O ,/O essentially/O restoring/O the/O original/O character/O ./O
In/O ``/O The/O Real/O Housewives/O of/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O ,/O he/O supposedly/O marries/O Selma/LOCATION ,/O but/O the/O relationship/O falls/O apart/O when/O Selma/LOCATION discovers/O Tony/PERSON only/O held/O a/O ceremony/O to/O make/O her/O his/O goomar/O as/O he/O is/O already/O married/O to/O another/O woman/O ./O
./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON 's/O actual/O name/O is/O the/O source/O of/O some/O dispute/O ,/O as/O several/O different/O real/O names/O have/O been/O revealed/O over/O the/O course/O of/O the/O series/O ./O
In/O the/O third-season/O episode/O ``/O Bart/O the/O Murderer/O ''/O ,/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON is/O referred/O to/O in/O a/O news/O report/O given/O by/O Kent/PERSON Brockman/PERSON as/O ''/O `/O William/PERSON ''/O '/O ''/O ''/O `/O Fat/O Tony/O ''/O '/O ''/O ''/O `/O Williams/PERSON ''/O '/O ,/O presumably/O an/O alias/O ./O
In/O the/O eighth-season/O episode/O ``/O The/O Homer/O They/O Fall/O ''/O ,/O the/O announcer/O at/O Homer/ORGANIZATION Simpson/ORGANIZATION |/ORGANIZATION Homer/ORGANIZATION 's/O boxing/O match/O against/O List/O of/O celebrities/O in/O The/O Simpsons/O #Drederick/O Tatum/O |/O Drederick/PERSON Tatum/PERSON refers/O to/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON as/O ''/O `/O Anthony/PERSON D'Amico/PERSON ''/O '/O -LRB-/O incidentally/O the/O name/O of/O one/O of/O the/O three/O Re-Recording/O Mixers/O in/O the/O end/O credits/O -RRB-/O ,/O which/O he/O is/O called/O later/O as/O well/O ,/O for/O example/O ,/O by/O the/O FBI/ORGANIZATION ./O
In/O the/O twelfth-season/O episode/O ``/O Insane/O Clown/O Poppy/O ''/O ,/O List/O of/O recurring/O The/O Simpsons/O characters/O #Frankie/O the/O Squealer/O |/O Frankie/PERSON the/PERSON Squealer/PERSON claims/O that/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON 's/O birth/O name/O is/O ''/O `/O Marion/PERSON ''/O '/O ,/O a/O reference/O to/O actor/O John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON 's/O real/O name/O ,/O Marion/PERSON Robert/PERSON Morrison/PERSON ./O
-LRB-/O 2009/O -RRB-/O ./O
Commentary/O for/O ``/O Insane/O Clown/O Poppy/O ''/O ,/O in/O ''/O The/O Simpsons/O :/O The/O Complete/O Twelfth/O Season/O ''/O -LSB-/O DVD/O -RSB-/O ./O
20th/O Century/O Fox/PERSON ./O
was/O cast/O as/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON because/O Sheldon/PERSON Leonard/PERSON was/O unavailable/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON first/O appeared/O in/O the/O third/O season/O episode/O ``/O Bart/O the/O Murderer/O ''/O ./O
The/O writers/O conceived/O the/O episode/O before/O the/O film/O ''/O Goodfellas/O ''/O ,/O which/O has/O a/O similar/O plot/O ,/O was/O released/O ./O
However/O ,/O when/O it/O was/O ,/O the/O writers/O incorporated/O references/O to/O the/O film/O in/O the/O episode/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON was/O modeled/O on/O Paul/PERSON Sorvino/PERSON ,/O who/O played/O mobster/O Paul/PERSON Cicero/PERSON in/O ''/O Goodfellas/O ''/O ./O
The/O appearance/O of/O Springfield/ORGANIZATION Mafia/ORGANIZATION #Legs/O and/O Louie/PERSON |/PERSON Louie/PERSON ,/O one/O of/O Tony/PERSON 's/O henchmen/O ,/O was/O based/O on/O another/O ''/O Goodfellas/O ''/O actor/O ,/O Joe/PERSON Pesci.Moore/PERSON ,/O Rich/PERSON -LRB-/O 2003/O -RRB-/O ./O
Commentary/O for/O ``/O Bart/O the/O Murderer/O ''/O ,/O in/O ''/O The/O Simpsons/O :/O The/O Complete/O Third/O Season/O ''/O -LSB-/O DVD/O -RSB-/O ./O
20th/O Century/O Fox/PERSON ./O
The/O end/O of/O the/O episode/O portrays/O a/O TV/O movie/O about/O the/O events/O depicted/O in/O the/O episode/O ,/O in/O which/O Joe/PERSON Mantegna/PERSON will/O play/O Fat/O Tony/PERSON -LRB-/O this/O was/O before/O it/O was/O decided/O that/O Fat/O Tony/PERSON would/O be/O a/O recurring/O character/O -RRB-/O ./O
The/O writers/O originally/O wanted/O Sheldon/PERSON Leonard/PERSON to/O voice/O Fat/PERSON Tony/PERSON ./O
When/O they/O were/O unable/O to/O get/O him/O ,/O they/O went/O with/O Joe/PERSON Mantegna/PERSON ./O
It/O is/O his/O longest-running/O role/O ./O
Fat/O Tony/PERSON was/O also/O voiced/O by/O Phil/PERSON Hartman/PERSON in/O the/O episode/O ``/O A/O Fish/O Called/O Selma/O ''/O ./O
IGN/ORGANIZATION ranked/O Fat/O Tony/PERSON at/O #/O 18/O on/O their/O 2006/O list/O of/O the/O ``/O Top/O 25/O ''/O Simpsons/O ''/O Peripheral/O Characters/O ''/O ./O
*/O ''/O `/O Feng/O Meng/Beng/O Meng/O -LRB-/O Peng/PERSON Meng/PERSON -RRB-/O ''/O '/O ,/O or/O ''/O `/O Fengmeng/O ''/O '/O ,/O -LRB-/O After/O his/O wife/O Chang/PERSON '/O e/O consumed/O the/O elixir/O of/O immortality/O ,/O Houyi/PERSON realized/O that/O he/O would/O never/O again/O be/O immortal/O and/O would/O soon/O die/O ./O
He/O resolved/O to/O pass/O his/O knowledge/O and/O skills/O of/O archery/O and/O hunting/O to/O the/O next/O generation/O to/O ensure/O that/O they/O would/O live/O after/O his/O death/O ./O
In/O order/O to/O do/O so/O ,/O he/O decided/O to/O take/O an/O apprentice/O ,/O Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON ;/O this/O apprentice/O soon/O became/O an/O expert/O archer/O but/O even/O so/O he/O was/O still/O envious/O of/O Houyi/PERSON 's/O superior/O abilities/O ,/O especially/O after/O a/O fateful/O archery/O competition/O in/O which/O Houyi/PERSON killed/O as/O many/O geese/O as/O Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON did/O with/O his/O archery/O despite/O having/O a/O far/O more/O difficult/O target/O ./O
Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON made/O multiple/O attempts/O on/O his/O old/O master/O 's/O life/O ;/O tried/O to/O ambush/O him/O with/O his/O bow/O and/O arrow/O only/O for/O Houyi/PERSON to/O stop/O his/O arrows/O with/O a/O return/O volley/O ./O
Finally/O ,/O Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON resorted/O to/O the/O use/O of/O a/O stick/O made/O from/O a/O peach/O tree/O to/O bludgeon/O his/O master/O to/O death/O ./O
Other/O stories/O are/O told/O of/O Peng/PERSON Meng/PERSON ,/O set/O in/O times/O previous/O to/O or/O after/O this/O fateful/O event/O ./O
In/O one/O telling/O ,/O told/O during/O the/O Chinese/O `/O Mooncake/O Festival/O '/O or/O Mid-Autumn/O Festival/O ,/O Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON -LRB-/O rendered/O in/O this/O translation/O as/O Peng/PERSON Meng/PERSON -RRB-/O ,/O was/O the/O cause/O of/O Chang/PERSON `/O e/O 's/O fateful/O decision/O to/O consume/O the/O elixir/O of/O immortality/O herself/O instead/O of/O sharing/O it/O with/O him/O ./O
In/O this/O telling/O ,/O Feng/PERSON Meng/PERSON attempted/O to/O steal/O the/O elixir/O of/O immortality/O from/O Chang/PERSON '/O e/O by/O force/O while/O Houyi/PERSON was/O out/O ./O
As/O she/O realized/O that/O she/O could/O n't/O defeat/O him/O ,/O Chang/PERSON '/O e/O escaped/O the/O only/O way/O she/O could-by/O consuming/O the/O elixir/O of/O immortality/O and/O ascending/O to/O the/O heavens/O where/O he/O could/O n't/O reach/O her.http/O :/O //O //O www.thenewcanadians.com/CULTURE/mooncakefestival.htm/O |/O years/O =/O 1983/O -/O |/O first/O =/O |/O last/O =/O |/O classification/O =/O The/O Young/O and/O the/O Restless/O cast/O members/O #Recurring/O cast/O |/O Present/O ;/O recurring/O |/O crossover/O =/O ''/O The/O Bold/O and/O the/O Beautiful/O ''/O |/O books/O =/O |/O spinoffs/O =/O |/O alias/O =/O Lauren/PERSON Fenmore/PERSON Baldwin/PERSON |/O born/O =/O 1964/O |/O death/O =/O |/O occupation/O =/O Co-CEO/O of/O Fenmore/PERSON 's/O Department/ORGANIZATION Stores/ORGANIZATION Member/O of/O the/O Board/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Directors/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Newman/ORGANIZATION Enterprises/ORGANIZATION Former/ORGANIZATION Partner/ORGANIZATION in/O Glo/O by/O Jabot/ORGANIZATION Boutique/ORGANIZATION Formerly/ORGANIZATION worked/O at/O Spectra/ORGANIZATION Fashions/ORGANIZATION in/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O California/LOCATION Formerly/O worked/O at/O Forrester/ORGANIZATION Creations/ORGANIZATION in/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O California/LOCATION |/O home/O =/O Genoa/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION ,/O Wisconsin/LOCATION |/O family/O =/O Fenmore/PERSON |/O wife/O =/O |/O husband/O =/O |/O father/O =/O Neil/PERSON Fenmore/PERSON |/O mother/O =/O Joanna/PERSON Manning/PERSON |/O halfsisters/O =/O Jill/PERSON Abbott/PERSON |/O sons/O =/O |/O aunts/O =/O Dot/O |/O nephews/O =/O |/O nieces/O =/O -RCB-/O -RCB-/O ''/O `/O Lauren/PERSON Fenmore/PERSON ''/O '/O is/O a/O fictional/O character/O from/O the/O American/O CBS/ORGANIZATION soap/O opera/O ''/O The/O Young/O and/O the/O Restless/O ''/O ./O
Introduced/O by/O William/PERSON J./PERSON Bell/PERSON ,/O the/O character/O made/O her/O debut/O during/O the/O episode/O airing/O on/O January/O 21/O ,/O 1983/O ,/O portrayed/O by/O Tracey/PERSON E./PERSON Bregman/PERSON ./O
In/O 1992/O ,/O Bregman/PERSON brought/O the/O character/O to/O ''/O The/O Bold/O and/O the/O Beautiful/O ''/O ,/O resulting/O in/O her/O migrating/O there/O fully/O in/O 1995/O ./O
The/O character/O was/O first/O married/O to/O private/O investigator/O Paul/PERSON Williams/PERSON -LRB-/O Doug/PERSON Davidson/PERSON -RRB-/O for/O two/O years/O ./O
Much/O of/O Lauren/PERSON 's/O history/O on/O both/O soap/O operas/O revolves/O around/O her/O rivalry/O with/O villain/O Sheila/PERSON Carter/PERSON -LRB-/O Kimberlin/PERSON Brown/PERSON -RRB-/O ./O
